all right so we're here to talk about
好吧，我们在这里谈论
spring cloud Java
Spring CloudJava
I'm sorry cloud native Java spring cloud
对不起，云原生Java spring cloud
services I'm Craig walls a little bit
我是克雷格墙的服务
about me I'm where I'm project leaf or
关于我，我在哪里，我要叶或
Spring social but I'm also been more
春季社交，但我也更喜欢
recently working a lot on the spring
最近在春季工作很多
cloud services team I also I believe was
我也相信云服务团队
wearing this shirt at spring one last
春季最后穿这件衬衫
year when I presented and just for you
我为您准备的那一年
guys if you come to my talk tomorrow
各位，如果你明天来我的演讲
I'll wear it again just just for you
我会再穿一次
okay
好的
I'm gonna hand it off now Scott
我要交了，斯科特
Frederick he's a colleague on the same
弗雷德里克（Frederick）他是同一个同事
team doing some of the same stuff we're
团队在做一些和我们一样的事情
gonna talk about today so it Scott yep
今天要谈论，所以斯科特
and I've been working on Cloud Foundry
我一直在研究Cloud Foundry
for about three years and been a user of
大约三年了，并且是
spring for a long time and now on the
春天很长一段时间，现在
spring engineering team for about a year
春季工程团队大约一年
so sort of in-between cloth boundary and
所以在布的边界和
spring so this is day two and we're
春天，所以这是第二天，我们
getting towards the end of day two in
在第二天结束时
this conference so we hope most of you
这次会议，所以我们希望大家
have heard something about cloud native
听说过有关云原生的一些信息
architecture spring cloud net flix OSS
体系结构Spring Cloud网flix OSS
and Cloud Foundry
和Cloud Foundry
if you think Jan yeah a few things how
如果你认为扬耶是几件事
many of you have gone to either Dave and
你们中的许多人去过戴夫和
Josh's spring cloud intro talk or John
Josh的Spring Cloud简介演讲或John
and Taylor's spring cloud and Netflix
还有泰勒的春天云和Netflix
talks most of you good all right better
你们大多数人说话很好
question how many of you haven't oh so
质疑你们中有几个没有
we can make up stuff and you guys would
我们可以弥补的东西，你们会
not know okay great because we're sort
不知道很好，因为我们很排序
of basing this talk on top of some of
在一些演讲的基础上
the stuff that you may have heard from
您可能从中听到的东西
them already so we're not gonna review a
他们已经，所以我们不会审查
lot of what spring cloud is in the intro
简介中介绍了很多春季云内容
to spring cloud we hope you've heard
到春天的云，我们希望你已经听到
some about that already but we're gonna
一些已经可以了，但是我们要
talk about is some value that we've been
谈论的是我们一直以来的一些价值
adding on top of spring cloud so we've
在春天的云之上添加，所以我们已经
been building this little product called
一直在制造这个叫做
spring cloud services and it is spring
春天的云服务，这是春天
cloud but it's sort of a curated
云，但有点像策展
opinionated implementation of spring
自以为是的春季实施
cloud developed for Cloud Foundry so the
为Cloud Foundry开发的云
idea is you don't have to go to open
想法是你不必去打开
source and get all the spring cloud open
采购并获得所有的春季云
source bits and then stand all that up
源位，然后站起来
yourself we can help you with that and
您自己，我们可以帮助您，并且
there's sort of three main goals we had
我们有三个主要目标
with building this product they were
通过构建此产品，他们
ease-of-use security and reliability and
易于使用的安全性和可靠性以及
we're going to go into some detail about
我们将详细介绍
what we mean by each of those but what
我们每个人的意思是什么，但是
we've implemented is three pieces of
我们已经实现了三个方面
spring cloud config server service
春季云配置服务器服务
registry and circuit breaker
注册表和断路器
and again we're gonna go into a lot of
再一次，我们将进入很多
detail about what those three things are
关于这三件事的细节
so this isn't gonna be a product pitch
所以这不会成为产品推销
we're not trying to tell you everything
我们不是想告诉你一切
about how great this product is although
关于这个产品有多棒
we think it is pretty great we're doing
我们认为我们正在做的很棒
really cool yeah it is really cool we're
真的很酷，是的，我们很酷
gonna get into the details of how you
要去了解你的细节
use it what the code looks like to
使用它，代码看起来像
consume it we're gonna get down and talk
消耗掉它，我们要下去说话
about Java code and and spring stuff and
关于Java代码和Spring的东西，以及
things like that as we go through this
经历这样的事情
talk so let's start off with these of
谈谈，让我们从这些开始
yous alright so for those of you who've
你们还好，所以对于那些已经
seen the talks already on spring cloud
看到已经在春季云上谈论
or maybe you've used spring cloud you
也许您已经用过Spring Cloud了
know that there's a couple of things you
知道你有几件事
have to do in order to use spring cloud
为了使用弹簧云必须要做的事情
I mean certainly you have to write your
我的意思是肯定你必须写你的
services that are going to bind
将要绑定的服务
themselves to the service registry are
自己到服务注册表
registering themselves with the service
向服务注册
registry or discover other services from
注册或发现其他服务
the service registry you know you're
您知道的服务注册表
gonna have to do things like you know
必须要做像你知道的事情
get your properties from a centralized
从集中式获取您的资产
configuration server you know that
您知道的配置服务器
you're going to annotate some of the
您将要注释一些
methods in your services as circuit
您的服务中的电路方法
breakers so that they'll failover so
断路器，以便他们进行故障转移
that they'll report metrics and then you
他们会报告指标，然后您
can go to the history dashboard or the
可以转到历史记录仪表板或
circuit breaker dashboard later on and
断路器仪表板稍后
see the details of what's going on there
查看发生了什么的细节
but you also have to do something else
但是你还必须做点别的
you also have to go stand up these
你也必须站起来
services these these individual servers
为这些单独的服务器提供服务
yourself you have to go create a project
你自己，你必须去创建一个项目
basically to create your own micro
基本上创建自己的微
sorrel micro service app that does
sorrel微服务应用程序
little more than something along the
只不过是沿着
lines of enable config server or enable
启用配置服务器或启用行
history dashboard or enable the was it
历史记录仪表板或启用它
discovery server Eureka server whichever
发现服务器Eureka服务器
one that is you have to do those at
一个是你必须做那些
those at and remember the annotations -
那些在并记住注释的人-
yeah you've got to remember the
是的，你必须记住
annotations the reason I'm trouble
注释我麻烦的原因
struggling with is they changed them at
挣扎的是他们改变了他们
one time and my brain is still stuck on
一次，我的大脑仍然停留在
the old version but you have to remember
旧版本，但您必须记住
to stand those up and deploy those as
站起来，将它们部署为
well as your application so essentially
以及您的应用程序
you're not only writing the the services
您不仅在编写服务
that make up your application you're
组成您的应用程序
also writing these other things
也写这些东西
basically infrastructural pieces the the
基本的基础设施
service registry in the dashboard and
仪表板中的服务注册表和
all these things that if I'm doing it
所有这些事情，如果我在做
and Scott's working on a project and he
斯科特（Scott）正在从事一个项目，他
has to do
必须做
and you guys are doing the same thing
你们在做同样的事情
you're gonna we're all gonna have to do
你要我们都要做
the same thing and the big question is
同样的事情，最大的问题是
why if everybody has to do that why does
为什么如果每个人都必须这样做，为什么
everybody have to do it why can't this
每个人都必须这样做，为什么不能
just happened on its own and so if
只是自己发生的，所以如果
you're working with spring cloud
您正在使用Spring Cloud
services that is exactly what can happen
正是可能发生的服务
instead of standing those things up
而不是站起来
yourself you can use Cloud Foundry use
自己可以使用Cloud Foundry使用
the CF command line or as I'm you can
CF命令行或按照我的意愿
also use the as I'm gonna show later you
也要使用，因为我稍后会显示给您
can use the dashboard and you can look
可以使用仪表板，您可以查看
you can go in there and you can create a
你可以去那里，你可以创建一个
service create a service registry
服务创建服务注册表
service create a circuit breaker
服务创建断路器
dashboard service create a config server
仪表板服务创建配置服务器
service and then bind those services to
服务，然后将这些服务绑定到
the individual micro services that are
个别的微服务
part of your application again much like
您的应用程序的一部分又像
you know what spring boot does for you
你知道 spring boot 帮你做什么
much like what spring cloud itself also
就像春天的云本身一样
does for you in many ways spring cloud
可以为您带来很多好处
services also just takes it a step
服务也迈出了一步
further back and enables you to focus on
再往后走，让您专注于
the what on building the services for
为什么建立服务
your app and not really worried on but
您的应用程序并没有真正担心，但是
standing up all this infrastructure that
支撑所有这些基础设施
it's gonna make them work but when it
它会让他们工作的，但是当它
comes time to actually creating the the
是时候实际创建了
client application you essentially just
客户端应用程序您实际上只是
do what you would have normally done you
做你通常会做的事情
create those client applications you
创建那些客户端应用程序
create a spring boot app you have the
创建一个您拥有的Spring Boot应用
spring Cloud starters you you would have
您将拥有的Spring Cloud Starters
to decide whether or not you're going to
决定你是否要
use eureka first configure or config
首先使用eureka进行配置或配置
first bootstrapping but when you using
第一次启动，但是当您使用
spring cloud services instead you
Spring Cloud Services代替您
basically create the spring boot app you
基本上创建您的Spring Boot应用程序
have the starters and then you bind your
有先手，然后你绑定你的
service to those individual micro
为那些个人微服务
service you bind the eureka server or
您绑定eureka服务器的服务或
the service registry service to the
服务注册表服务
services in your app and now those are
应用中的服务，现在这些是
the config server and now your micro
配置服务器，现在你的微型
services can consume those other
服务可以消耗其他
services just as any other service just
就像其他服务一样
like they might consume a Postgres
就像他们可能会消耗Postgres
database or a or a Redis database or or
数据库或或Redis数据库或或
AMQP or something that some other
AMQP或其他
service they can consume eureka they can
他们可以消耗尤里卡的服务，他们可以
consume with a config server they can
使用配置服务器可以
consume the history dashboard in the
使用历史记录仪表板
same way so one of the things that in
同样的方式之一是
addition to saving you the trouble of
除了省去你的麻烦
having to stand these services up
必须站起来这些服务
yourself
你自己
is we also save you the trouble of
是我们还为您省去了
having to secure them because I'm not
必须保护它们，因为我不是
talking about your your micro service
谈论您的微服务
I'm talk about again these
我再说这些
infrastructural services
基础服务
if you want to stand up at Eureka server
如果你想在尤里卡服务器站起来
that's great you can do that and now you
太好了，您可以做到，现在您
have to worry about who else is going to
不必担心还有谁
consume those services in there who's
在那里消费那些服务的人
going to come in there looking for your
要进去找你
service and then be able to consume it
服务，然后能够使用它
who else is going to be able to come in
还有谁能进来
and look at your config server and ask
并查看您的配置服务器并询问
it for the configuration and how they
它用于配置以及它们如何
can consume it if it's if you've stood
如果你站着就可以食用
this up and you've put this out on Cloud
这个，你已经把它放到云端了
Foundry
铸造厂
what's stopping someone else from
是什么阻止了别人
hitting that same service and asking it
击中相同的服务并询问
for the configuration or the services
用于配置或服务
that it offers and so that's where
它提供的，所以在那里
spring cloud services has gone to the
春天的云服务已经到了
trouble of securing these for unit does
确保这些为单位的麻烦
it with OAuth essentially these the
它与OAuth本质上是这些
OAuth credentials are exposed via
OAuth凭证通过公开
service bindings so when you bind your
服务绑定，因此当您绑定自己的
the service to your your application or
为您的应用程序提供服务或
to your micro service as part of that
作为您的微服务的一部分
binding it's going to include a number
绑定它将包含一个数字
of things one of those is a URL through
其中之一就是通过
which you can do a client credentials
你可以做一个客户凭证
binding it's going to provide the client
绑定它将为客户提供
credentials themselves and you're going
凭证自己，你要去
to be able to go get an OAuth access
才能获得OAuth访问权限
token from there and be able to then
从那里的令牌，然后能够
from there consume those services but if
从那里消耗那些服务，但是如果
somebody else has some other service you
别人还有其他服务
know somebody else comes and tries to
知道有人来尝试
hit your config server service or tries
点击您的配置服务器服务或尝试
to hit the service registry service
打服务注册表服务
they're not going to know those
他们不会知道那些
credentials they're not going to
他们不会去的凭证
necessarily know that URL it's gonna be
一定知道URL将会是
a lot harder in fact hopefully do
事实上，希望这样做会更加困难
impossible for them to actually consume
他们不可能真正消费
that unless they are authorized to do so
除非他们被授权这样做
because they were bound to the to those
因为他们被那些
services and this is really important
服务，这真的很重要
for enterprise customers especially
特别适合企业客户
because some companies have this luxury
因为有些公司有这种奢侈
of being able to say all of our micro
能够说出我们所有的微观
services and our service registry are
服务和我们的服务注册中心是
all running inside of our control
全部运行在我们的控制之内
network so we're just gonna trust
网络，所以我们只是信任
everything and if you get to live in
一切，如果你住
that world that's really awesome but a
这个世界真的很棒，但是
lot of enterprises they really can't say
他们真的不能说很多企业
that the security people come around and
安全人员到处走走
say just because it's running in our
之所以说是因为它正在我们的计算机中运行
internal network we can't trust
我们无法信任的内部网络
everything that's going on we need a lot
发生的一切我们都需要很多
more security built around what
围绕什么建立更多的安全性
for example Netflix Yurika can do all on
例如Netflix Yurika可以在
its own so that's some of the stuff we
它本身就是我们的一些东西
built on top yeah the the mistake in the
建立在最上面，是
security obviously is that even though
安全显然是即使
you're behind the wall doesn't mean
你在墙后面并不意味着
you're secure so you know a lot of the
您很安全，所以您了解很多
security breaches happen because someone
发生安全漏洞是因为有人
inside the wall was able to get to stuff
墙上的东西能够塞满东西
so
所以
it's an ordinal your own attention
这是你自己注意的序数
intentionally or unintentionally it's
有意或无意地
important to be able to still lock those
重要的是能够仍然锁定那些
down even though you're not on a public
即使你不在公开场合
cloud we meant to mention earlier
我们本来要提到的云
actually we'd love for this to be
其实我们很想成为
interactive so if you have questions
互动式的，如果您有任何疑问
raise your hand or yell and we'd be glad
举起你的手或大喊，我们将很高兴
to take the questions as they come we
在问题来临时，我们
have a Q&amp;A section at the end of this
在此末尾有一个问答部分
talk but that don't mean you have to
说话，但这并不意味着您必须
wait till then just go ahead and yeah
等到那再继续吧
I'll just just will only ask one thing
我只会问一件事
is if you do have a question raise your
是如果您有问题要提出
hand really high and speak really loud
手真的很高，说话声音很大
because it's a bigger room we can hear
因为这是一个更大的房间，我们可以听到
you yeah and well we'll feel free to
是的，我们随时可以
answer any question you have
回答任何问题
we might answer it with a question and
我们可能会提一个问题并回答
answer you didn't like but we'll do our
回答您不喜欢的问题，但我们会尽力而为
best
最好
here's one right here
这是一个
yeah so this is all leveraging Cloud
是的，这都是利用云
Foundry right let me repeat the question
代工权让我重复这个问题
he wants to know is that you're going
他想知道是你要去
from different you know development to
从不同的你知道发展到
QA to production or whatever levels of
生产或任何级别的质量检查
migration you have of your of your
您的移民
application he wants know if is is how
他想要知道的应用程序是如何
seamless is it for you to do this to go
顺其自然吗
from one to the other you know and are
从一个到另一个你知道并且是
you you're hitting a different Eureka
你打不同的尤里卡
you're hitting a different config file
您正在击中其他配置文件
is it pretty for you to move from one
从一个方向上走对你来说很漂亮
environment to the other and I think I
环境到另一个，我想我
know the answer I'll let Scott answer it
知道答案，我会让斯科特回答
I'm gonna give you the short answer I
我要给你一个简短的答案
think it's really easy go ahead yeah it
认为这真的很容易，是的
is and it's timely question because
是，这是及时的问题，因为
we're on this Cloud Foundry slide so all
我们在此Cloud Foundry幻灯片上，所以所有
of this is based on running this stuff
这是基于运行这些东西
on Cloud Foundry and part of the benefit
在Cloud Foundry上，部分收益
we get from that is this reliability
我们从中得到的是这种可靠性
where Cloud Foundry automatically makes
Cloud Foundry自动制造的地方
sure these services we're deploying or
确保我们正在部署这些服务或
staying up and running all the time in
一直保持运转
your apps that are consuming them or
您正在使用它们的应用程序，或者
another facet of that to answer your
另一个方面来回答你的
question is cloud foundry has this
问题是Cloud Foundry有这个
concept of organizations and spaces so
组织和空间的概念如此
you might create an organization for
您可以创建一个组织
development an organization for QA and
建立质量检查组织，并
an organization for production and maybe
生产组织，也许
one for staging and then you can deploy
一个进行分期，然后就可以部署
your applications to those awards and
您对这些奖项的申请，以及
spaces individually as you progress them
在进行进度时逐个空格
through so you might have developers
通过这样您可能会有开发人员
pushing to the development organization
推动发展组织
and then continuous integration
然后持续整合
pipelines pushing to all the other ones
管道推向其他所有管道
so you'd be creating instances of these
所以你要创建这些的实例
services we're talking about and pushing
我们正在讨论和推动的服务
your apps to those different orgs and
将您的应用发送给其他组织
spaces as you progress them through
通过它们前进的空间
development to production so we can give
发展到生产，所以我们可以给
you more demos of Cloud Foundry and how
您更多有关Cloud Foundry的演示以及如何
it works and spaces work you can
它可以工作，空间可以工作
actually see some of that in the lounge
实际在休息室看到一些
I think if you want to and it's kind of
我想如果你愿意的话
the beauty of being able to bind to a
能够绑定到一个美丽
service as opposed to refer to a service
服务而不是指服务
but you know explicitly by the URL is
但您通过URL明确知道的是
the the one consuming the service has no
消费服务的人没有
idea where that service is until it's
知道该服务在哪里
told by the binding and so if there's
告诉绑定，所以如果有
this level of indirection between
之间的这种间接级别
between them so it doesn't need to know
他们之间，所以它不需要知道
until it needs to know and so as you
直到它需要知道
move from one environment to the other
从一种环境转移到另一种环境
as the binding takes takes hold that's
因为绑定需要保持
that's how it knows where Eureka is
这样便知道尤里卡在哪里
that's how it knows where the config
这样便知道配置在哪里
server is you'll be able to see that one
服务器是您将能够看到一个
we get to do in some demos here in a few
我们将在这里进行一些演示
minutes yeah
分钟
right now when you do the service
当您进行服务时
provisioning you just do CF create
供应您只需执行CF创建
service and we're creating stuff in the
服务，我们正在
background you don't say I want to scale
你不说我要缩放的背景
up that service we're managing how its
该服务，我们正在管理其
run and how its scaled in the background
运行以及它在后台如何缩放
behind the scenes so in our GA version
在幕后，所以在我们的GA版本中
we're gonna provide one instance of each
我们将为每个提供一个实例
of the services we provide and then I'm
我们提供的服务中，然后
in subsequent releases we'll start to
在后续版本中，我们将开始
introduce some of the h.a capabilities
介绍一些ha功能
and having multiple instances of running
并有多个正在运行的实例
and things like that
诸如此类的事情
I'm not gonna talk about timelines right
我不会谈论时间表
now we can know it's closer than that
现在我们知道它比那更近
that's in our we're getting ready to do
那是我们准备做的事
a 100 release of this that's worth
值得的100版本
saying it's in public beta right now
说它现在处于公开测试阶段
we'll have a 100 release in a matter of
我们将在100个发行版本中
weeks probably and we're talking about
大概几个星期，我们正在谈论
that sort of stuff for 1.1 or maybe as
这种东西为1.1或也许
far out as 1.2 but no further than that
远远超过1.2，但不超过
it's one of our most requested features
这是我们最需要的功能之一
that we don't have in the beta right now
我们现在没有Beta版
is is a little bit more high
高一点
availability than we're providing in the
可用性比我们在
beta and the 1l suffice it to say this
beta和1l就足够了
is not the first time today we've talked
今天不是第一次
about it yeah yeah ok so you're gonna
关于它，是的，好的，所以你要
hear us
听我们说
use this term service broker a lot so we
经常使用这个术语服务经纪人，所以我们
just want to give you a little bit of an
只想给你一点
overview what a service broker is and
概述什么是服务代理，以及
why we're gonna use that term so much
为什么我们要这么多使用这个术语
now so Service Worker is a way to extend
现在，Service Worker是一种扩展方式
cloud foundries base functionality to
云代工厂的基本功能
provide resources to your applications
为您的应用程序提供资源
so the most typical kinds of services
所以最典型的服务
that are provided by brokers are
由经纪人提供的是
relational databases MongoDB Redis
关系数据库MongoDB Redis
rabbitmq all those sorts of things that
所有这些东西
you can imagine an application might
你可以想象一个应用程序可能
want to consume so all of our services
想消费，所以我们所有的服务
are provided by a service broker that we
由我们提供的服务经纪人提供
wrote Cloud Foundry knows how to talk to
撰写Cloud Foundry知道如何与之交谈
a service broker through a rest
通过休息的服务经纪人
interface it's a very simple interface
界面这是一个非常简单的界面
there's actually a leaf sixth REST API
实际上有第六个REST API
call now there's a fairly new one that
现在打电话，有一个相当新的
we didn't put on the slide so how can
我们没有放幻灯片，如何
our Cloud Foundry will call your service
我们的Cloud Foundry将致电您的服务
broker and ask it for a catalogue of all
经纪人，并要求所有的目录
the services you're providing and from
您提供的服务以及来自
then on when somebody says I want to
然后有人说我想
create a service of type
创建类型的服务
if Cloud Foundry knows that that service
如果Cloud Foundry知道该服务
is the one you're providing then it'll
是您要提供的那个
call this provision service endpoint and
将此提供服务端点称为
at that time you're supposed to create
那时您应该创建
whatever resources you need as a service
您需要的任何资源作为服务
broker and then when an application
经纪人，然后当一个应用程序
wants to consume that service there's
想要使用该服务
this create binding call that's made and
这个创建的绑定调用
all that really does is return to the
真正要做的就是返回
application all the connection details
应用所有的连接细节
and the credentials that it needs to
及其所需的凭据
talk to that service instance so you can
与该服务实例交谈，以便您可以
create one instance of a given service
创建给定服务的一个实例
that have multiple apps bound to it so
绑定了多个应用程序，因此
that's the difference between
那是之间的区别
provisioning and binding and then of
供应和绑定，然后
course you can unbind apps from services
您当然可以取消服务与应用程序的绑定
and you can delete service instances and
您可以删除服务实例和
the new call is update so you can say I
新电话是更新的，所以你可以说我
want to change some aspect of a service
想改变服务的某些方面
instance in Cloud Foundry can do that
Cloud Foundry中的实例可以做到这一点
now if Cloud Foundry doesn't care where
现在，如果Cloud Foundry不在乎
a service broker is deployed you just
您只是部署了一个服务代理
deploy your service broker code
部署服务代理代码
somewhere and then you register it with
某个地方，然后您向其注册
caught foundry with a URL and some
用URL和一些捕获的铸造
credentials and then it just starts
凭据，然后就开始了
calling it it also doesn't care what
称它也不在乎什么
your service brokers are written in it
您的服务经纪人都写在里面
can be written in Java or NGO or Python
可以用Java或NGO或Python编写
or PHP I don't know why you do that but
或PHP，我不知道为什么要这么做，但是
you can write it anything you want
你可以随便写
deploy it anywhere you want and then you
部署到您想要的任何地方，然后您
just register it to Cloud Foundry so
只需将其注册到Cloud Foundry，以便
even if you can do it in PHP I would
即使您可以用PHP做到这一点，我也会
yeah it's not recommended yeah but
是的，不推荐，但是
what's really cool about this I mean
我的意思是什么真的很酷
never you know outside the scope of this
从来没有你知道超出这个范围
talk we're we're talking about spring
谈论我们，我们谈论春天
cloud services just the fact that you
云服务只是您
can kind of kind of create your own
可以有点创建自己的
services just by creating a service
仅通过创建服务即可获得服务
broker is a nice feature at Cloud
经纪人是Cloud的一个不错的功能
Foundry itself and so just just the nice
铸造厂本身，所以只是好的
ability for you to extend your your
您扩展您的能力
experience in Cloud Foundry so if you're
拥有Cloud Foundry的经验，所以如果您
running on pivotal Web Services or
在关键的Web服务上运行或
pivotal cloth foundry or probably any
关键的布料铸造厂或其他
other Cloud Foundry distribution there's
其他Cloud Foundry发行版
a way that you can see a services
您可以看到服务的方式
marketplace and this is an example of
市场，这是一个例子
what one of those screens might look
这些屏幕可能看起来是什么
like this is from pivotal claw foundry
像这样来自关键爪铸造厂
so you can see all these services listed
这样您就可以列出所有这些服务
here each of these boxes are something
这里每个盒子都是
that's been exposed from some service
从某些服务中暴露出来的
broker so you can see ours on here we
经纪人，所以你可以在这里看到我们的
have circuit breaker
有断路器
we have config server and service
我们有配置服务器和服务
registry all three of those services are
注册表中所有这三个服务都是
provided by our broker all the rest of
由我们的经纪人提供的所有其他
them on they're provided by other
他们由其他人提供
individual brokers so it's a really nice
个人经纪人，这是一个非常好的
way to expand out the capabilities of
扩展功能的方式
Cloud Foundry through the service broker
通过服务代理进行Cloud Foundry
mechanism so let's talk about our
机制，让我们谈谈我们的
service broker that we wrote we wrote
我们写的服务经纪人我们写的
our service
我们的服务
brogre in Java because Java is awesome
Java中的brogre，因为Java很棒
we use spring extensively because spring
我们广泛使用spring是因为spring
is even more awesome so we made those
更棒，所以我们做了那些
implementation choices and our service
实施选择和我们的服务
broker which makes it interesting to
经纪人，这对
talk about in this talk because we're
在这个话题中谈论，因为我们
providing you lots of cool things you
为您提供许多很酷的东西
can use when you're building your job of
在您建立工作时可以使用
spring apps and we used all exactly
春天的应用程序，我们完全使用了
those same things to build this broker
同样的事情来建立这个经纪人
that's providing those services to you
为您提供这些服务
so we implement the service broker API -
因此我们实现了服务代理API-
Cloud Foundry and we had to do this
Cloud Foundry，我们必须这样做
interesting thing where when Cloud
有趣的是，何时云
Foundry calls a service broker to
铸造厂致电服务经纪人
provision a new service instance it
提供一个新的服务实例
gives that service broker 60 seconds to
给那个服务经纪人60秒
provision that service instance and if
设置该服务实例，如果
the broker doesn't respond in 60 seconds
经纪人在60秒内没有回应
saying apps created we're good to go
说创建的应用很不错
then it assumes something has gone wrong
那么就假设出了点问题
some of the services we're provisioning
我们正在提供的一些服务
take longer than 60 seconds so we
需要超过60秒，所以我们
implemented this little async mechanism
实现了这个小的异步机制
where when Cloud Foundry calls our
Cloud Foundry打电话给我们的地方
broker and says provision of service
经纪人并说提供服务
instance we return almost immediately
实例，我们几乎立即返回
and say yeah sure we did it everything's
并说是的，我们确实做到了一切
good and all we do in the meantime is
好，与此同时我们要做的是
put a message on a rabbit queue and then
将消息放在兔子队列上，然后
we return to Cloud Foundry and say
我们回到Cloud Foundry说
everything's good
一切都很好
then we have this second application
然后我们有第二个应用程序
that's listening on that rabbit queue
在兔子队列上听
that does all the real work of
完成了所有的真正工作
provisioning that service instance so
设置该服务实例，以便
then later when an application comes to
然后稍后当一个应用程序进入
bind to that service instance if it
绑定到该服务实例（如果有）
tries to bind and that worker is still
试图绑定，那个工人仍然
doing its thing then it's just going to
做它的事，那只会
get an error saying instance isn't ready
收到错误消息，指出实例尚未准备就绪
to be bound yet or if something goes
被束缚，或者如果发生了什么
horribly wrong in the instance can't be
实例中的严重错误不可能是
created then it'll get an error but
创建的话会得到一个错误，但是
otherwise when the service is ready to
否则，当服务准备好
go then we reply back on the message
走，我们回覆讯息
queue when the broker gets a ok message
当经纪人收到确定消息时排队
so it knows that it can start being
所以它知道它可以开始被
bound to so this little async mechanism
必然会出现这种异步机制
is a nice little thing we put in place -
是我们准备的一件好事-
to separate those two responsibilities
分开这两个职责
using RabbitMQ between them which is a
他们之间使用RabbitMQ
micro-services design pattern so that
微服务设计模式
all works really nicely for us newer
一切对我们来说都很好
versions of Cloud Foundry actually have
版本的Cloud Foundry实际上有
made this async provisioning mechanism
制定了这种异步配置机制
official so when we're running on newer
官方，所以当我们运行更新
versions of Cloud Foundry we have a way
版本的Cloud Foundry我们有办法
to tell it we didn't quite create a yet
告诉我们我们还没有创建一个
we're in the works and you can keep
我们正在努力，您可以继续
calling us back and asking us if we're
打电话给我们，问我们是否
done yet
做完了
so that async mechanism is being made
这样就形成了异步机制
official
官方
foundry and newer releases so what this
代工和较新版本，这是什么
worker app does when it's asked to
工作人员应用程序在被要求执行时
provision the service instance is it
提供服务实例
pushes apps to Cloud Foundry so both of
将应用程序推送到Cloud Foundry，因此
these apps here this broker app and this
这些应用程序在这里这个经纪人应用程序和这个
worker app are applications deployed to
辅助应用程序是部署到的应用程序
Cloud Foundry and what they do is deploy
Cloud Foundry及其工作是部署
more applications to Cloud Foundry so
Cloud Foundry有更多应用程序，因此
now we're getting in this Java spring
现在我们进入了Java的春天
Cloud Foundry inception thing going on
Cloud Foundry成立之初
here so when you say I want to provision
在这里，所以当你说我要供应
a new service registry service what
一个新的服务注册服务什么
we're doing in the background is pushing
我们在后台做的推
an instance of spring cloud Netflix
Spring Cloud Netflix的实例
Eureka to Cloud Foundry and then
尤里卡到Cloud Foundry，然后
returning you the route to where that
返回您去那儿的路线
service is when you go to bind to it
服务是当您绑定到它时
this gets to the reliability thing we
这关系到我们的可靠性
were talking about these brokers are
在谈论这些经纪人是
running on Cloud Foundry all the service
在Cloud Foundry上运行的所有服务
instances we create are just apps
我们创建的实例只是应用程序
running on Cloud Foundry so everything
在Cloud Foundry上运行，因此一切
is going to stay up through Cloud
将通过云保持熬夜
Foundry as health management and
铸造作为健康管理和
everything works really well yeah it's a
一切都很好，是的
it's as if all those things that you
好像所有这些东西
would have to do manually without spring
没有弹簧就不得不手动做
cloud services it's as if we wrote them
云服务，就像我们编写它们一样
for you and deployed them for you and I
为您，并为您和我部署它们
see I use the word as if loosely it's
看到我用这个词好像是松散地
not as if it's actually what happened we
不像是我们实际上发生了什么
wrote those and now our service broker
写那些，现在是我们的服务经纪人
and worker app will deploy those for you
工作人员应用会为您部署这些
and I mentioned that we wrote it in Java
我提到我们是用Java编写的
using spring so this is a little
使用弹簧，所以这有点
inventory of the pieces of spring that
弹簧片的库存
we use all of our apps or spring boot
我们使用所有我们的应用程序或 spring boot
the broker app the worker app all of the
经纪人应用程式，工作人员应用程式
service instance backing apps are all
服务实例支持的应用都是
spring boot and they use different
spring boot ，他们使用不同的
pieces and parts of spring cloud
Spring Cloud的碎片
depending on the functional and
取决于功能和
functionality that are providing they
提供他们的功能
use spring cloud connectors to talk to
使用弹簧云连接器与之交谈
rabbitmq and the service broker actually
Rabbitmq和服务经纪人实际上
has a little my sequel database that it
有一点我的续集数据库
stores its view of what services have
存储其对哪些服务的看法
been provisioned and all that so we use
已配置，因此我们使用
spring cloud connectors to talk to that
弹簧云连接器与之交谈
database we use spring security and
数据库我们使用Spring Security和
spring security OAuth 2 extensively and
Spring Security OAuth 2广泛和
Craig will show a little bit of that and
克雷格（Craig）将展示一点，
the demo of what that looks like
外观的演示
functionally but all the OAuth stuff we
从功能上讲，但我们所有的OAuth内容
do is using spring store spring security
做的就是使用spring store的spring security
OAuth 2 we use spring data JPA to talk
OAuth 2我们使用Spring数据JPA进行交谈
to that little my sequel database I
到我的那个小续集数据库
mentioned we use spring a spring AMQP
提到我们使用弹簧AMQP弹簧
for all of our RabbitMQ interaction
对于我们所有的RabbitMQ互动
between our apps so we're using as much
在我们的应用程序之间，因此我们使用了尽可能多的
spring stuff as we possibly can
尽我们所能
now we also use this nice little project
现在我们也使用这个不错的小项目
called spring boots EF service broker
叫 spring boot EF服务经纪人
and it's basically just a spring MVC
基本上只是春天的MVC
application that
申请
that service broker arrests API so if
该服务经纪人逮捕了API，因此，如果
you want to write your own service
你想写自己的服务
broker in Java using spring this is a
使用Spring的Java中的中间人
little starter project and you just can
小小的入门项目，您就可以
implement your real business logic of
实施您的真实业务逻辑
your broker without having to worry
您的经纪人，不必担心
about what are all the rest in points
关于其余的一切
I'm supposed implemented what HTTP
我应该实现什么HTTP
return codes do I return in this
返回码我要在这返回吗
situation or that situation based on
情况或基于
what the spec says all that stuff is
规格说明所有这些内容是
implemented for you it's really nice
为您实现了它真的很好
little library which is open source and
小图书馆是开源的
then we use Cloud Foundry Java client
然后我们使用Cloud Foundry Java客户端
the way that you talk to Cloud Foundry
与Cloud Foundry交谈的方式
to push apps and manage things in Cloud
推送应用程序并管理Cloud中的事物
Foundry rather it's the command-line
代工，而是命令行
tool or the app manager or anything else
工具或应用程序管理器或其他任何东西
is through Cloud Foundry REST API and
通过Cloud Foundry REST API和
this last library is just a nice Java
最后一个库只是一个不错的Java
binding to that REST API so if you're a
绑定到该REST API，因此，如果您是
Java app you can push apps delete apps
您可以推送应用程序的Java应用程序删除应用程序
do all sorts of things like that inside
在里面做各种各样的事情
a Cloud Foundry okay so now we're gonna
Cloud Foundry好吧，现在我们要
start talking about each of these three
开始谈论这三个
services individually and we'll give you
单独提供服务，我们会给您
a quick overview of what they do and
他们所做的事的简要概述
then we'll do some demos of them so when
然后我们将对它们进行一些演示，以便当
you say I want to provision a which one
你说我想提供一个
is this container of a config server
这是配置服务器的容器吗
when you say you want to provision a
当您说要提供一个
config server instance what you get is a
配置服务器实例，您得到的是
instance of a spring cloud config server
Spring Cloud配置服务器的实例
that we push to Cloud Foundry behind the
我们将Cloud Foundry推到了
scenes for you that spring cloud config
为您准备的场景，春天的云配置
server can either be backed by a git
服务器可以由git支持
repository or a subversion repository
仓库或Subversion仓库
and the things that are in spring cloud
还有Spring Cloud里的东西
can fix server that we support our
可以修复我们支持我们的服务器
search paths within a config repo so if
搜索配置库中的路径，因此如果
you've got a repo with all your code in
您有一个包含所有代码的存储库
it and one subdirectory within that repo
它和该存储库中的一个子目录
is your config information you can point
是您可以指出的配置信息
us to just that one subdirectory and
我们只是一个子目录，
we'll just take configure information
我们将获取配置信息
from there and we support basic off to
从那里开始，我们支持基本
the back-end repo when the extra
后端回购时，额外
security we've implemented here beyond
我们已经在此处实施的安全性
just an app that wants to talk to config
只是想与配置对话的应用
server has to have the OAuth token
服务器必须具有OAuth令牌
provided in the credentials from the
凭证中提供的
bind we just make sure that only
绑定，我们只确保仅
applications that are using our binding
使用我们的绑定的应用程序
can talk to that config server so if we
可以和那个配置服务器通话，所以如果我们
provision an inch of an instance of a
提供一英寸实例
config server and you want some other
配置服务器，你想要一些其他
app that's not using our libraries to
没有使用我们的库的应用程序
talk to it that won't work because you
跟它说那行不通，因为你
don't know how to do all the OAuth
不知道如何做所有的OAuth
handshaking so you have to use our
握手，因此您必须使用我们的
binding to get to it and that's an extra
绑定到它，这是一个额外的
level of security and then we haven't
安全级别，然后我们还没有
talked much about
谈论了很多
starters yet let me get to this last one
入门者，但让我讲到最后一个
and then we'll answer your question so
然后我们会回答您的问题
you've probably seen the spring cloud
你可能已经看过春天的云
starters and this concept of starters
起动器和起动器的概念
and spring is just a way to pull in one
春天只是一种吸引人的方式
dependency and get a dependency graph
依赖关系并获取依赖关系图
pulled into your application without
拉入您的应用程序而无需
having to have the whole list of things
必须拥有全部清单
that you need to pull in so we have
你需要拉进去，所以我们有
starters for each of our services we're
我们为每项服务提供的服务
providing and this starter for config
提供和此启动器的配置
server automatically looks at this
服务器自动查看
binding that you got from config server
您从配置服务器获得的绑定
goes out and talks to that config server
出去和那个配置服务器对话
and creates a property source that's
并创建一个
backed by all the configuration settings
由所有配置设置支持
in that configs River so you had one
在那个河里，所以你有一个
dependency to your build file and you
依赖于您的构建文件，您
bind a config server instance to your
将配置服务器实例绑定到您的
application and all of those things in
应用程序以及所有这些东西
that back configuration are just
后面的配置只是
automatically available in your app yeah
在您的应用程序中自动可用
question
题
yeah so the question is we support this
是的，所以问题是我们支持这一点
being backed by you to get in subversion
得到您的支持以进行颠覆
today are there plans to support other
今天有计划支持其他
things
东西
so everything in spring cloud is about
所以春天云里的一切都是关于
an abstraction layer with
具有的抽象层
implementations underneath that
在下面的实现
abstraction layer so spring cloud
所以春天云抽象层
provides this config server abstraction
提供此配置服务器抽象
layer it provides the git and subversion
提供git和subversion的层
implementations of that that's all the
那就是所有的实现
implementations provided in the
中提供的实现
open-source project so far so those are
到目前为止的开源项目
the ones we're leveraging as more get
我们正在利用的更多
added to the open-source project
添加到开源项目
we'll pull those into this product as
我们会将它们拉入产品
well so that's kind of the way the
好吧，这就是
released rain flows and actually the
释放的雨水实际上
subversion implementation wasn't written
颠覆实现未编写
by the maintainer zuv spring cloud that
通过维护者zuv spring cloud，
was written by somebody else and then
是别人写的，然后
committed or submitted as a contribution
承诺或作为贡献提交
because they wanted subversion support
因为他们想要颠覆支持
so just a little plug for open-source
所以只是一点点开源插件
contribution absolutely Donuts it's not
贡献绝对是甜甜圈
all written by pivot all the others the
所有由枢轴写所有其他
first version part of this wasn't
第一部分不是
written by pivotal so if somebody has a
由关键编写，所以如果有人有一个
need for one of those write it
需要其中之一写
contributed the open-source and as soon
贡献了开源，并尽快
as is available in open-source so we can
就像开源中提供的那样
pull it into this product well sounds
将其拉入产品听起来不错
really cool how does this work Scott
真的很酷，斯科特如何运作
it's all magic creo que well let's see
都是神奇的创意，让我们来看看
let's see what kind of magic well you've
让我们看看你有什么样的魔力
probably seen this is basically the same
可能看到这基本上是相同的
kind of diagram you'd see whether you're
那种图，你会看到你是否
using spring cloud services or just
使用春季云服务还是
regular spring cloud configs config
常规的Spring Cloud Configs配置
server but essentially you you take and
服务器，但实际上您是
you put your your application
你把你的申请
configuration into a repository such as
配置到诸如
git or subversion notice that's not an
git或subversion注意不是
octa cat up there so it doesn't have to
八哥猫在那里，所以不必
be github it can be any git repository
是github它可以是任何git仓库
including one that's inside of your
包括你里面的一个
firewall you put your configuration
您配置的防火墙
properties in there and this enables you
属性在那里，这使您能够
to do a number of things primarily
主要做一些事情
enables you to version it and evolve
使您能够对其进行版本控制和发展
your properties independently of your
独立于您的财产
application and which is a kind of a
应用程序，这是一种
nice feature when you're when you're
当你在的时候很好的功能
doing configuration I mean if you put if
做配置，我的意思是如果你把
you put your configuration in in
您将配置放入
environment variables it's a little
环境变量有点
tricky to version those things if you
如果您很难将这些东西版本化
put your configuration as hard-coded
将您的配置设置为硬编码
within your application now they have to
在您的应用程序中，现在他们必须
evolve at the same pace as the
以与
application and probably have to be in a
应用程序，可能必须在
micro services based app gonna have to
基于微服务的应用将不得不
be duplicated across multiple apps so
可以跨多个应用程序复制，因此
instead you put them in git or
相反，您将它们放入git或
subversion and what happens is this you
颠覆，这是怎么回事
tell spring cloud configuration server
告诉Spring Cloud配置服务器
where the
在哪里
repository is and where to find those
仓库是什么以及在哪里找到这些
and it's going to take those properties
并将采用这些属性
it's gonna suck those in and then it's
它会吸那些，然后
going to just make them available to
只是将它们提供给
whatever apps or micro services need
任何应用程序或微服务需要
those in and that are bound to that that
那些与之相关的
config server and then it's as if they
配置服务器，然后就像他们
were part of the properties file or
是属性文件的一部分，或
environment variables or what have you
环境变量或你有什么
it's just it's just another set of
这只是另一组
properties that are available to that
可用的属性
application to use as they see fit so
他们认为合适的应用
let me show you a demo a little demo
让我给你看一个演示
with this now I'm gonna go ahead and
现在，我要继续
tell you a couple of caveats of this
告诉你一些注意事项
demo upfront first off we are running
首先演示我们正在运行
this not on the public pivotal Web
这不在公共枢纽网上
Services cloud foundry we're running
我们正在运行的服务云代工厂
this on an internal set of environments
这在内部环境中
we work on for a pivotal Cloud Foundry
我们致力于建立关键的Cloud Foundry
our PCF Cloud Foundry that we we run
我们运营的PCF Cloud Foundry
internally so therefore I am logged into
内部，因此我已登录
a VPN right now so who knows what could
VPN，现在谁知道
happen in that context conference Wi-Fi
在这种情况下发生会议Wi-Fi
VPN conference what could possibly go
VPN会议可能会发生什么
wrong
错误
so one of the things I do also know is
所以我也知道的一件事是
that occasionally the browser likes to
有时浏览器喜欢
complain to me about certificates on
向我投诉有关的证书
those servers ignore those hopefully
这些服务器希望忽略它们
I've got past those before I got in here
我进来之前已经过去了
but in case you see those it's not it's
但是如果你看到的不是
not a problem with the config server
配置服务器没有问题
it's a problem with just the fact that
这是一个问题，事实是
we're running on a test environment see
我们正在测试环境中运行，请参见
what was the other thing I was going to
我要做的另一件事是什么
tell you oh I didn't want to go through
告诉你哦，我不想经历
the exercise the full exercise of
练习
standing this stuff up in front of you
站在你面前的东西
because that at some point it gets
因为在某个时候
boring I'll work you through kind of a
无聊的我会通过
mocked up scenario first and then I'll
首先模拟场景，然后我将
show you what we really have going on
告诉你我们真正发生了什么
here so let me switch over find another
在这里，让我切换寻找另一个
window to work in there we go finally we
在其中工作的窗口，我们终于走了
see good finally we see something maybe
终于看到好了，也许看到了一些东西
let's see let's go let's go to gonna
让我们一起去吧
show you stuff that's on this this one
给你看这个东西
first so I'm logged into this machine
首先，我登录到这台机器
called read that we call we named them
称为阅读，我们称我们为它们命名
after colors so this is red and I'm in
在颜色之后，所以这是红色，我在
my seawalls org and let's just say I
我的海堤组织，让我们说我
have this one app I'm not gonna fully
有这个应用程序，我不会充分
bind II have this one simple app called
绑定二有一个简单的应用程序称为
hi let's just say I wanted to what looks
嗨，我们只是说我想看什么
like I've already added the config
就像我已经添加了配置
server let me delete that just so you
服务器让我删除它只是为了你
can see the full experience
可以看到完整的经验
and there we go yeah sure whatever it's
然后我们去确定是什么
a shame this is that warning was just
遗憾的是，警告只是
saying you've got an app bound to this
说您有一个与此相关的应用
thing you just deleted it so you might
你刚刚删除了它，所以你可能
have to restart that app so it realizes
必须重新启动该应用程序，以便它意识到
the other thing went away so here we
另一件事消失了，所以在这里我们
have all the different services I could
尽我所能提供所有不同的服务
I could select from so you see in here
我可以选择，所以你在这里看到
config server service registry circuit
配置服务器服务注册表电路
breaker we're talking with the config
断路器，我们正在使用配置
server right now so I'm going to pick
服务器现在，所以我要选择
this guy so here we are yeah this I'll
这个家伙，所以我们在这里，我会
pick this plan because the price is
选择这个计划，因为价格是
unavailable therefore my money is
无法获得，所以我的钱是
unavailable so I'll pick that will
无法使用，所以我会选择
select this plan and it's gonna want a
选择这个计划，它会想要一个
name for that instance so sure I'll call
该实例的名称，请确保我会打电话给
it a clever name like config server
它像配置服务器一样聪明的名字
seems like I've done this before it will
似乎我已经做到了
add it fantastic so now I can do really
添加它很棒，所以我现在可以真正做到
cool things and like I can come up here
很酷的东西，就像我可以来这里
and maybe bind it to my to my high
也许把它绑定到我的高处
application so let's try that and I'm
应用程序，所以让我们尝试一下，
gonna go pick the config server from the
要从中选择配置服务器
marketplace and bind it oh crap an error
市场并绑定它哦废话
happened well I'll tell you what
一切顺利，我会告诉你
happened the reason I'm even going
发生了我什至要走的原因
through the exercise of showing what
通过展示什么的练习
could go wrong is because I do this
可能会出错是因为我这样做
every time this is the probably the only
每次这可能是唯一的
time I've done it and realized that this
时间我已经做到了，意识到
was gonna happen
会发生
I always forget to do this I haven't
我总是忘记这样做
told it where get where my configuration
告诉它在哪里获取我的配置
is I haven't told it anything it so the
是我什么都没告诉过，所以
this service that needs to get its
该服务需要获得其
configuration from a git repository or a
从git仓库或
subversion repository has no idea where
颠覆存储库不知道在哪里
to go get this stuff from because I
去拿东西，因为我
didn't finish the setup for the config
没有完成配置的设置
server okay I didn't mean to go to
服务器好吧，我不是要去
marketplace sorry about that so I had to
市场对此感到抱歉，所以我不得不
go down a config server down here and
在这里关闭配置服务器
click on manage and of course I got a
点击管理，我当然有一个
login so give me a moment to deal with
登录，让我花点时间处理
this and then and I've conveniently
然后，我很方便
placed my passwords over here so I don't
将密码放在这里，这样我就不会
have to go look them up every time
每次都要去找他们
okay textmate decided to hide from me I
好吧，课友决定对我隐瞒我
say convenient that was old completely
说方便，完全是旧的
lie or this is awesome
说谎或这太棒了
anybody know how to get a window that's
任何人都知道如何获得一个
not on the screen up onto the screen
不在屏幕上，而是在屏幕上
here I'll do this
在这里我会做
bear with me while I copy my password
复制密码时请多多包涵
for blue I said I was going to do that
为了蓝色，我说我要去做
conveniently so I wouldn't have to look
方便，所以我不必看
it up turned like it turns out I had to
事实证明，我不得不
do that anyway all right yes so let's
无论如何都可以，是的，所以让我们
not deal with that at some point of time
在某个时间点不处理
that will be available they're actually
他们将实际上可用
running in the demo lounge on PWS who
在PWS的演示休息室中运行的人
are demoing that during this conference
在本次会议上演示
we sort of set it up there quickly to be
我们将其快速设置为
able to demo it but it's not ready to be
能够演示它，但还没准备好
production supported yet because we're
支持生产，因为我们
not even in GA so we'll be running on
甚至不在GA中，因此我们将继续
PWS for a couple of weeks and you can go
PWS几个星期，你可以去
see that in the demo lounge and then
在演示休息室看到，然后
we'll take it away and later on in the
我们将其拿走，然后在
year we'll have it deployed to PWS for
一年，我们将其部署到PWS
real all right so I managed to get the
真的很好，所以我设法得到了
the right password while Scott was
斯科特当时是正确的密码
talking I had copied the wrong one so I
说话我抄错了，所以我
got the right one I'm logged in and now
找到了我登录的正确帐户，现在
it's asking me for a choice of git or
要求我选择git或
subversion and some URLs and so I can
颠覆和一些URL，所以我可以
pick one or the other and I happen to
选择一个或另一个，我碰巧
have a git repository handy I'm just
我有一个git存储库
gonna go ahead and fill it in github
继续并在github中填写
calm slash kaboom slash my app config
冷静斜线kaboom斜线我的应用程序配置
notice I have the choice if I want to
注意，如果我想，我可以选择
selecting a specific branch default it's
选择一个特定的分支默认是
gonna be master of course that seems the
当然会成为大师
most natural choice if there is a path
如果有路径，这是最自然的选择
within that repository that I want to
在我想要的存储库中
dig into then I can do it by setting a
深入研究，然后我可以通过设置一个
search path there if I my repository
如果我的存储库在那里搜索路径
requires authentication I can give my
需要身份验证，我可以给我
username and password in this case it's
用户名和密码在这种情况下是
just a public github repository you're
只是一个公共的github存储库
free to go hit that URL in your browser
可以在浏览器中随意点击该URL
right now and you'll see what we're
现在，您会看到我们在做什么
looking at I don't it's not in a branch
看着我不是在树枝上
and there are no paths so I'm just going
而且没有路，所以我只是去
to click Submit and at this point the
单击提交，此时
config server is now set up and I can
现在已经设置好配置服务器，我可以
close out of this window I can come back
关闭此窗口，我可以回来
over here and I can go back to my app
在这里，我可以回到我的应用程序
and with any luck at all
并祝你好运
I can come over here bind the service
我可以过来绑定服务
and it's you know it's wanting me to do
你知道我要我做
a restage I'm not gonna bother doing
我不会打扰的休息
that because this is not the real demo
因为这不是真正的演示
the main thing I wanted to show you it's
我想告诉你的主要是
gonna kick that I'm gonna do it I could
我会踢，我会做
restart this to a restage it kick off
重新启动它以重新启动它
and then that app now have access to it
然后该应用现在可以访问它
instead what I've done is I've done a
相反，我要做的是
very similar thing already before we
我们面前已经有非常相似的事情
came in here go to blue hope it doesn't
进来这里去蓝色希望它不会
ask me to log in again that would be
请我再次登录
horrible and I already have an app out
太糟糕了，我已经有一个应用了
here it's the I don't know if you've
这是我不知道你是否已经
seen it or not it's the fortune teller
看到与否这是算命先生
example Matt Stein I believe is one who
我相信马特·斯坦的例子
wrote it
写了
you may have seen it one of his talks
您可能已经看过他的演讲之一
you may have also seen it out at the
您可能也已经在
pivotal lounge we just decided to
我们刚刚决定的关键休息室
leverage that since it's kind of
利用它，因为它是
familiar to a lot of people and so what
很多人都熟悉，又如何
I have deployed I here are two services
我已经部署了，这里有两项服务
are two apps I have the fortune UI and
我拥有财富UI的是两个应用程序，
the fortune service we're going to talk
我们要谈论的财富服务
a little bit later when we talk about
稍后，当我们谈论
the discovery server how these guys talk
发现服务器这些家伙如何交谈
to each other how they discover each
彼此如何发现彼此
other and work together the main thing I
其他和我一起努力的主要事情
want to focus on right now is the fact
现在想专注于事实
that the Fortune Service is bound to the
财富服务已绑定到
config server and the config server as
配置服务器和配置服务器为
when I click on manage of course it's
当我点击“管理”时
gonna ask me to log in naturally that
要我自然登录
would that would make sense while people
人们会这样做吗？
are watching me and it's gonna show me
在看着我，它会告诉我
in fact that I am set up on git I'm
事实上，我在git上设置了
hitting actually the repo in Matt's
实际击中Matt的回购
github space and that's what's being
github空间，这就是事实
bound to that so I've already done this
绑定到那个，所以我已经做到了
previously and if I were to go to let's
以前，如果我要去让我们
see here's the fortune teller app we'll
看到这里是算命应用程序
talk more about that in a minute look at
稍后再详细讨论
the env for the environment for it and
环境的环境
you can see right up here at the top
你可以在这里的顶部看到
among all the other properties that are
在所有其他属性中
being made available to this application
可用于此应用程序
including things from properties files
包括属性文件中的内容
and from vcap and environment variables
以及来自vcap和环境变量
and system properties and whatnot right
和系统属性，什么不对
up here at the top you can see that it's
在顶部，您可以看到它是
actually pulling in stuff from that
实际从中吸取东西
github repo and so you see the spring
github repo，所以你看到了春天
profiles you see some more interestingly
您看到更有趣的个人资料
to me you see some stuff regarding
对我来说，你看到一些有关
Eureka and different you know the lease
尤里卡和其他人你知道租约
renewal interval
更新间隔
and things like that so these are things
像这样的东西
that are not hard-coded in in the
没有硬编码在
fortune teller out they are instead out
算命先生出来，而不是
there in in github and because this
在github中，因为这
application is bound to a configuration
应用程序绑定到配置
server that is pulling its configuration
正在拉其配置的服务器
data from that git repository it's as if
那个git仓库中的数据就好像
we put these in a properties file or set
我们将它们放入属性文件或设置
them in an environment variable as part
作为环境变量的一部分
of this app but they're external the app
这个应用程式，但它们在应用程式外部
and therefore it can be versioned
因此可以对其进行版本控制
independent of this app so that's that's
与这个应用程式无关，所以就是
essentially the the example we're gonna
本质上是我们要去的例子
stop we're a stop kind of put a pause on
停下来，我们停下来，停下来
this example for now we're going to talk
这个例子现在我们要谈
a little bit about eureka now our our
关于尤里卡的一点现在我们
discovery server service registry so
发现服务器服务注册表，因此
that's where scott picks up all right so
那是斯科特接好的地方，所以
with service registry what you get is a
与服务注册表，您得到的是
spring cloud netflix eureka instance
spring-cloud-netflix尤里卡实例
pushed as an app to Cloud Foundry for
作为应用程序推送到Cloud Foundry
you and there's a really important bit
你，还有一个非常重要的地方
of security we do here so if you know
出于安全考虑，我们在这里这样做，如果您知道
how Yuriko works basically an
百合子的工作原理基本上是
application can come up and it can
应用程序可以出现，它可以
register itself to eureka and say i'm a
向尤里卡注册并说我是一个
service that's available for somebody
某人可用的服务
else to discover and consume another app
其他发现和使用另一个应用程序
can come up and register again with the
可以提出并再次向
exact same name and say Here I am here's
完全相同的名字，说我在这里
my name I'm ready to be consumed if two
我的名字，我准备好被两个
apps come up and register themselves
应用程序出现并自行注册
with the same names the second was just
同名第二个就是
gonna overwrite the first so that can
要覆盖第一个，这样可以
happen accidentally just because two
偶然发生是因为两个
apps happen to pick the same name to
应用碰巧选择了相同的名称
register with or that can happen
注册或可能发生
maliciously because a second app is
恶意地是因为另一个应用
coming along and saying I'm gonna
来跟我说我要
masquerade is that first app and do a
假面舞会是第一个应用程序，
man-in-the-middle attack by stealing all
通过偷走所有中间人攻击
the traffic that's meant to go to one
这意味着要去的流量
service send it to me instead maybe do
服务发送给我，而不是做
something with it like store it off away
像东西一样存放起来
and then you know return what the other
然后你知道返回其他
service would have returned so there's a
服务将返回，所以有一个
this ability to do a man-in-the-middle
做中间人的能力
attack against eureka just because it
攻击尤里卡只是因为它
doesn't have that kind of security built
没有建立这种安全性
into it because a lot of people don't
因为很多人没有
need that you can just trust the
需要你可以相信
applications or keeping their name
申请或保留名称
straight and the nothing malicious is
直截了当，没有恶意
going on in the enterprise environment a
在企业环境中进行
lot of people care a lot that you can't
很多人在乎你不能
do that sort of man-in-the-middle attack
进行中间人攻击
or you can't unintentionally register
否则您将无意中注册
two things with the same names so the
具有相同名称的两件事，所以
security we put in place here is when an
我们在这里设置的安全性是
application registers with eureka and
申请在尤里卡和
says here's my name
说这是我的名字
we record some metadata along with that
我们记录一些元数据
registration including some information
注册包括一些信息
that is traveling along in this OAuth 2
在此OAuth 2中一起旅行
token anything else that wants to come
标记任何其他想要来的东西
up and update that registration record
并更新该注册记录
with the same name better have that same
同名更好地拥有相同的
of' token or it's not going to work
的令牌或它不起作用
they're gonna get an error and say you
他们会出错并说你
can't update this registration record so
无法更新此注册记录，因此
the first application that comes in with
附带的第一个应用程序
a name and registers with that name from
一个名称，并从中使用该名称进行注册
then on is the only application that can
然后是唯一可以
ever update any information about that
曾经更新有关的任何信息
registration again it's a really
再次注册，这是一个真正的
important bit of security that we've
我们拥有的重要安全性
added on top of the open source spring
在开源弹簧的顶部添加
cloud and Netflix and then we also have
云和Netflix，然后我们还有
a starter for spring cloud service
Spring Cloud服务的入门者
registry and that automatically
注册表，并自动
configures the client side of eureka
配置尤里卡的客户端
with the information that's in the
与其中的信息
service credentials with where the
服务凭证与
eureka server is and what the oauth2
尤里卡服务器是什么和oauth2
token is you need to talk to it or the
令牌是您需要与之对话还是
client ID and makes all that stuff wired
客户端ID，并将所有内容连接起来
up automatically so how does that work
自动启动，这如何工作
it's just magic Craig magic Wow
这只是魔术克雷格神奇的哇
probably should have had Michael
大概应该有迈克尔
Carducci join us for this talk in that
Carducci与我们一起进行本次演讲
case but anyway we're here we go this is
情况，但无论如何我们在这里，这是
this is again a very familiar picture to
这又是一张非常熟悉的照片
you and it'll walk through the example
您，它将通过示例
in a minute we have this that you saw
一分钟后，您就会看到
when I pulled up the in Cloud Foundry on
当我在Cloud Foundry上拉起
blue you saw we had a fortune teller UI
蓝色，您看到我们有一个算命UI
and fortune teller service both of those
和算命服务
are individual applications deployed
是已部署的单个应用程序
into Cloud Foundry and so a fortune
进入Cloud Foundry等行业
teller service comes along and fortune
柜员服务伴随着财富
teller service is bound to the service
柜员服务绑定到该服务
registry and it says hey hello my name
注册表，它说嘿你好我的名字
is fortune teller service and here's
是算命服务，这是
where I live here's how people can
我住的地方人们可以
contact me if they need me just let me
如果他们需要我，请与我联系
know let them know where I'm at and so
知道让他们知道我在哪里等等
fortune teller UI later needs to consume
算命UI以后需要使用
that service and so fortune teller UI
该服务以及算命UI
also bound to the service registry says
也绑定到服务注册表说
hey tell me a little bit about where the
嘿，告诉我一些关于
fortune teller you service is where can
算命先生您可以在哪里服务
I find one of these and so it asked that
我找到其中之一，所以它问
question in the service register it
服务中的问题将其注册
responds simply by saying this right
只需说出这一权利即可做出回应
here I'm sure everybody can read that
在这里，我相信每个人都能读懂
just fine actually that's a that's an
很好，实际上那是一个
abridged version of it it's just an XML
它的删节版只是XML
set of information that comes back and
一组返回的信息
tells more than you would ever want to
告诉你比你想要的更多
know about that service including if
了解该服务，包括是否
multiple instances of that service where
该服务的多个实例，其中
it can find each of those instances at
它可以在以下位置找到每个这些实例
and so the fortune teller your eyes you
所以算命先生注视着你
eye basically takes that information
眼睛基本上会获取该信息
uses it to make a call over to fortune
用它来发财
teller service and says hey give me a
柜员服务，说嘿给我
random fortune it makes kind of a call
随机的运气有点像电话
like this and what's really cool about
这样，真正有趣的是
this especially if you're using spring
这尤其是如果您使用弹簧
cloud if you've ever know if you've used
如果您曾经使用过云，
spring cloud to do this or not but if
春天的云是否这样做，但如果
you have you've seen that when you
你有看到，当你
you've given a rest template and with
您已经提供了一个休息模板，并带有
rest template you can actually make a
休息模板，您实际上可以制作一个
get request or a post request or
获取请求或发布请求，或
whatever type of request you need to
无论您需要哪种类型的请求
make to not the actual physical URL on
而不是实际的实际网址
Cloud Foundry which you really don't
您真的不喜欢的Cloud Foundry
even need to know instead you make a
甚至需要知道相反，你做一个
call to the service name slash whatever
调用服务名称斜杠
the path is so here it's making a call
路径就这样在这里打电话
to fortune service under the cover some
为了掩盖财富服务
magic is happening and it's you know
魔术正在发生，这是你知道的
discover it's looking this information
发现它正在查找此信息
up from the clouds from the canoe
从独木舟的云层中升起
service registry and then it's able to
服务注册表，然后它能够
map that to the actual physical URL but
将其映射到实际的物理URL，但是
in your code you don't need to know
在您的代码中，您不需要知道
where it's physically bound to you just
在身体上绑定到你的地方
simply say hey make a call make this get
只是说嘿打个电话就可以了
request to fortune service give me some
请求财富服务给我一些
give me a random fortune from that so
从那给我随机的财富
let me show you a little bit more about
让我向您展示更多有关
that and also reminded me while Scott
那也让我想起了斯科特
was talking there's something I failed
在说我失败了
to show you I meant to but I completely
告诉你我的意思，但我完全
forgot about it in the config server and
在配置服务器中忘记了它，
it's also the same thing I'm going to
这也是我要去的事情
show you here but applies to the other
在这里显示，但适用于其他
services as well such as the service
服务，例如服务
registry so I don't wanna look at red
注册表，所以我不想看红色
anymore let's look at blue we have the
再来看看蓝色我们有
config server here let's see the config
配置服务器在这里，让我们看看配置
server as I said is bound to loops I
我所说的服务器必然会循环
click the wrong one I love it when I do
当我点击错误的按钮时，我会爱上它
the wrong thing it's you can see it's
错误的事情是你可以看到
it's bound here to the fortunate service
它绑定到了幸运的服务
and so it's part of that binding now you
所以这是现在绑定的一部分
don't generally don't need to mess with
通常不需要
this but it is available for you look at
这个，但是你可以看一下
as part of this binding I can go into
作为绑定的一部分，我可以进入
show credentials and in there what you
显示凭证，在那里您可以看到
see is the access token URL or the
请参阅访问令牌URL或
access token URI from which a this at
访问令牌URI，从中获取this
this particular application this fortune
这个特殊的应用这个财富
service can go get a token
服务可以获取令牌
to be able to use this so as I'm sorry
能够使用它，对不起
so a client can get this application can
这样客户可以获取此应用程序
get me a client to the config server
带我一个客户端到配置服务器
request this token and now it can
请求此令牌，现在它可以
consume data from the config server
使用配置服务器中的数据
without this and without the client ID
没有这个，没有客户ID
without the client secret there is no
没有客户的秘密就没有
way that you're gonna be able to
这样您将能够
actually consume this from the config
实际上从配置中消耗了这个
server because of that security if we go
服务器，因为这种安全性，如果我们去
look at the that's kind of the same
看看那是一样的
thing for the service registry you're
服务注册表的事情
gonna see kind of the same sort of deal
会看到类似的交易
going on although it's kind of hidden at
继续，尽管它有点隐藏在
the moment probably some weird thing
当下可能有些奇怪的事情
going on about there we go
继续那里，我们去
you're gonna see that in fact it also
你会发现实际上
has an access token URI a client ID and
具有访问令牌URI和客户端ID，并且
a client secret there is no way that
客户秘密是不可能的
anyone else coming along is going to be
其他任何人都会成为
able to go hit that service registry and
能够进入该服务注册表并
request services by their name without
以他们的名字请求服务而无需
actually having a good token for that
实际上有一个好的代币
and so in this case the fortun service
因此在这种情况下，幸运的服务
wanting to consume that is going to use
想要消耗将要使用的
this URL give it this client ID and
这个网址给它这个客户ID和
secret it's going to do an OAuth client
秘密要做一个OAuth客户端
credentials grant it's gonna get back a
凭证授予它可以取回
token and then it's gonna be able to
令牌，然后它将能够
make use that token on every single
在每一个上使用该令牌
request to the service registry to ask
要求服务注册中心询问
for services or to bind itself we our
为了服务或约束自己，我们
register itself within the service
在服务中注册自己
registry and when we say the client app
注册表以及当我们说客户端应用程序时
needs to take those three things and
需要采取这三件事，
create that token you don't have to
创建您不需要的令牌
write the code that that's what is in
编写其中的代码
that spring cloud services starter you
那个春天的云服务可以使您兴奋
pull that as in a dependency it's
像依赖中那样拉
already got all the code that knows how
已经有了所有知道如何做的代码
to take those three bits of information
吸收这三点信息
go talk to the wot server get the right
去与WOT服务器交谈得到正确的
token pull the token back into the
令牌将令牌拉回
client app and then pass that token with
客户端应用程序，然后使用
every call to each one of these servers
这些服务器中的每一个的每次呼叫
so that's not code you have no this is
所以这不是代码，你没有，这是
completely under the cover stuff I just
完全掩盖了我刚才所说的东西
want to kind of go in there and show you
想进去看看
kind of where you could see kind of
那种你可以看到的地方
what's happening under the covers and
幕后发生了什么事，
where you know where it's actually it
你知道它在哪里
gonna make this request for that token
会要求该令牌
but generally speaking you need not
但一般来说您不需要
worry about that all right so as you saw
担心一切都好，如你所见
I have the fortune service is bound to
我有运势必定
the service registry the likewise the
服务注册表同样
fortune UI is also apparently fun stuff
财富UI显然也很有趣
has happened while I was away is gonna
我不在的时候发生了
see a limit to app crash it's also
看到应用程序崩溃的限制
registered or bound to the service
注册或绑定到服务
registry and it has its own set of
注册表，它有自己的一套
credentials unique from those of the
凭证的唯一性
other of the of the the fortune service
其他的财富服务
so it's gonna be able to consume those
所以它可以消耗那些
as well now so what's different there
现在也一样，那里有什么不同
between the binding to the service and
与服务的绑定与
the binding to the UI essentially the
与用户界面的绑定本质上是
URI is gonna be the same but the client
URI将相同，但客户端
ID and secret are different because this
ID和机密不同，因为这
is a different client so those things
是一个不同的客户，所以那些事情
are unique per application that's bound
每个绑定的应用程序都是唯一的
to this service so that makes it
这项服务，使它
impossible for one app to kind of just
一个应用程序不可能只是
sniff and find out somebody else's
闻一闻，发现别人的
client ID right and as a consequence of
客户ID权利以及由于
that everything I showed you on that
我在那展示给你的一切
slide with all the arrows is going to be
滑动所有箭头将是
able to take place and so when we go
能够发生，所以当我们走
into the fortune-teller UI the
进入算命用户界面
fortune-teller UI is is and I'll show
算命用户界面是，我将展示
you some code here in a second a fortune
一会儿给你一些代码
teller your eye is going to be able to
柜员你的眼睛将能够
make that call to the service get a
致电服务获得
fortune back and display it on page and
返回并显示在页面上
you know you do learn a lot from your
你知道你确实从中学到了很多
mistakes one of those is I should have
错误之一是我应该有
made sure that the passwords were a
确保密码是
little easier to grab so that's a good
容易抓住，这是一个很好的
thing and I can hit refresh and it says
事情，我可以点击刷新，它说
if you feel you're right stand firm by
如果您觉得自己是坚定的立场
your convictions I'm pretty sure I was
你的信念我很确定我是
wrong so I'm not gonna mess with that
错了，所以我不会搞砸了
one you get the idea I'll show you a
一个你有主意，我会告诉你一个
little bit of the code that actually
实际上的一点点代码
makes this happen so shockingly not much
使这种事情发生得如此震惊
if you look at the the build file for
如果您查看构建文件
this for the fortune service you're
这是您的财富服务
gonna see in there among other things
会在那里看到
you're gonna see the starters for spring
你会看到春天的开端
cloud services config client and spring
云服务配置客户端和春季
cloud services service registry it has
它具有的云服务服务注册表
some other stuff necessary to kind of
一些其他必要的东西
make the app work but these are the
使应用程序正常工作，但这是
things that are going to bring in the
将会带来的东西
stuff that Scott spoke about to
斯科特谈到的东西
automatically you know bring all the
自动知道所有
dependencies necessary to make this work
进行这项工作所需的依赖项
bring in the property source so it knows
引入财产来源，以便它知道
where to get this stuff from indicates a
从哪里获得这些东西表示
config can take clients gonna be able to
配置可以使客户端能够
know to get the stuff from the config
知道从配置中获取东西
server and so forth and so when you go
服务器等等等等，当你走的时候
look at the code see where am I looking
看看代码，看看我在哪里
here
这里
yeah me and Scott went through this
是的，我和斯科特经历了这个
exercise yesterday and I couldn't I
昨天运动，我不能
remember looking at this thinking myself
记得自己看着这个想法
to calm my gosh there's like no code to
平静我的天哪，就像没有代码
talk about in fact you'll remember Scott
谈论事实上你会记得斯科特
I was looking up yeah oh yeah this is
我一直在看，是的，哦，是的
just domain there's nothing in here this
只是域，这里没有东西
these are just controllers there's
这些只是控制器，
nothing here these are just sir there's
这里没有什么，只是先生，有
nothing in here this is just application
这里没有什么，这只是应用程序
code boring stuff nobody cares about
没人关心的代码无聊的东西
right has nothing to do with of course
权利当然无关
it's the most important thing in your
这是你最重要的事情
app it has nothing to do with what we're
应用程序，它与我们无关
in cloud services the main thing we care
在云服务中，我们最关心的是
about is the fact that we've enabled
关于的事实是我们已经启用
Discovery client that one line right
发现客户那一行正确
here this this this is you know
这这这是你知道的
hands-down the most important thing in
放下最重要的事情
this this application that Java filed
这个Java提交的应用程序
this configuration class is it's what's
这个配置类是什么
enables the application to know to go to
使应用程序知道去
the discovery server to look up its
发现服务器以查找其
services and in this particular case
服务，在这种情况下
because it is the fortune service to
因为这是
register itself with us with the
向我们注册
discovery service how it registers
发现服务如何注册
itself that's gonna be down here do we
本身会落在这里吗
always forget where this is put in
永远忘记把它放在哪里
bootstrap you're gonna have a spring
引导你要有春天
application name is fortunes that's
应用程序名称就是
gonna be the name of the service so when
将成为服务的名称，所以当
we go look when the client I or when the
我们去看看客户我什么时候
UI starts looking this thing up it's
用户界面开始查找该东西
gonna look it up with the name fortunes
会用财富这个名字来查找它
and my slide set fortunes service do the
和我的幻灯片财富管理服务
mental mapping I probably should have
我可能应该有的心理测绘
fixed the slide to match this but it's
修复了幻灯片以使其与此匹配，但是
gonna look it up with the name fortunes
会用财富这个名字来查找它
as far as the cloud configuration it's
就云配置而言
gonna have a little bit of extra
会有一点额外的
information here I think this has been
我认为这里的信息已经
made easier lately about yeah the
最近让耶更容易了
starter will do that for you though yeah
入门者会为您做到的，是的
just yeah the starter is gonna take care
是的，入门者会照顾好
of this part for you so that's it for
这部分是给你的，仅此而已
the fortune teller service as far as the
算命先生服务
configuration notice there was no
配置通知没有
there's a site for a man able discovery
有一个供人发现的网站
client there was nothing in there to
客户那里什么都没有
enable config client it's because it's
启用配置客户端是因为
not really not necessary if that that
那样不是真的没有必要
starter is taking care of that business
入门者正在照顾那个生意
for you it's making sure that that
为您确保
stuff's available all right
东西都可以了
okay circuit breaker so the last service
好的断路器，最后的服务
is the circuit breaker dashboard
是断路器仪表板
hopefully you're all familiar with the
希望大家都熟悉
circuit breaker pattern you have service
您需要维修的断路器模式
a that needs to talk to service B and if
需要与服务B对话的a，如果
for some reason service B goes away you
由于某种原因，服务B离开了您
want service aid to act in some
希望服务援助在某些方面发挥作用
predictable and graceful way to the fact
可预测的优美方式
that it can't talk to service B anymore
它不能再与服务B通信了
so typically what you like to do is have
所以通常你喜欢做的是
some fallback mechanism where service a
服务的一些后备机制
can respond with some useful data to
可以用一些有用的数据来响应
whoever's calling it that may not have
可能没有的人
everything it could because it can't
因为它不能做的一切
talk to service B anymore
与服务B通话
so if that sort of circuit breaker
因此，如果这种断路器
pattern is in use and something is going
模式正在使用中并且正在发生
wrong you would want to be able to see
错误的，您希望能够看到
that that's going on first of all you
那首先发生在你身上
want that circuit breaker to be tripped
希望该断路器跳闸
automatically and second you want to be
自动，第二想成为
able to see that there's something
能够看到有东西
happening that's not the usual thing
发生这不是平常的事情
that's happening so that's what this
这正在发生，这就是这个
enables so when you provision a serve a
启用，因此当您提供服务时
circuit breaker or dashboard instance
断路器或仪表板实例
this is the most complex of our three
这是我们三个中最复杂的
services that's why we left it for last
服务，这就是我们将其留在最后的原因
you actually get three things I'm gonna
你实际上得到了三件事
tell you what these are real quick and
告诉你这些是真正的快速和
then we'll have a picture that'll show
然后我们将有一张图片显示
it much more clearly so you get an
它更清楚，所以你得到
instance of a spring cloud Netflix
春天云Netflix的实例
history dashboard this is the UI that's
历史信息中心，这是
going to give you a view of how things
让你对事物的看法
are running right now
现在正在运行
then you get an instance of spring cloud
然后你得到一个Spring Cloud的实例
Netflix turbine server and what turbine
Netflix涡轮服务器和什么涡轮
does is it a grits all metrics coming in
难道所有指标都会进来吗
from all the things that are hooked up
从所有连接的东西
to the circuit breaker and just brings
到断路器，并带来
them all into one central aggregation
他们都集中在一起
point so that this dashboard can read
点，以便此仪表板可以读取
that information out of it and then you
从中获取信息，然后您
get an instance of a pivotal rabbit &amp;
获取一个关键兔子的实例＆
hu service which is how those metrics
hué服务，这些指标如何
are sent to turbine so the picture will
被发送到涡轮，所以图片会
explain it much better and of course we
解释得更好，当然我们
have a starter that automatically wires
有一个自动接线的起动器
all this stuff up so your client can
所有这些东西，使您的客户可以
talk to the rabbit server and then the
与Rabbit服务器交谈，然后
rabbit Zurich and the turbine server and
兔子苏黎世和涡轮服务器和
Capone for mation off of rabbit so how's
卡彭（Kape）兔子的话，怎么办
this work Scott this is even more magic
这项工作斯科特，这甚至更神奇
and nobody can tell me about this magic
没有人能告诉我这种魔力
because I think you probably handle this
因为我认为你可能会处理
one better than I can
一个比我更好的
okay so these are the three components
好的，所以这是三个组成部分
that I was talking about a second ago we
我刚才在谈论
have your client applications on the far
在远处有您的客户端应用程序
left-hand side and then you have this
左边然后你有这个
cue that metrics are going to be put on
提示将要采用指标
to and then you have
到然后你有
turbine server in the middle this just
涡轮服务器在中间这只是
animates the things just start flowing
动画事物开始流动
right and then we have the history
对，然后我们有了历史
dashboard on the end so your client
最后的仪表板，这样您的客户
application is just sending metrics
应用程序只是发送指标
about how things are working on to this
关于事情如何发展
cue turbine takes all the metrics coming
提示涡轮采用所有即将来临的指标
from all the different client
来自所有不同的客户
applications puts them on one cue and
应用程序将它们放在一个提示上，
gives the historic stash board one place
给历史性的木板一个地方
to get all those from and then you get
从那里得到所有这些，然后你得到
this nice UI that tells you what
这个不错的用户界面，告诉您什么
services are up what services are down
服务上升什么服务下降
if service a is trying to call service B
如果服务a试图呼叫服务B
and it can't it's going to show you that
它不能告诉你
so those are how all those components
这些就是所有这些成分
work together yeah because what you're
一起努力，因为你在做什么
gonna have to do normally if you weren't
如果你不去的话就必须正常做
using spring cloud services you're gonna
使用Spring Cloud Services，您将
have to excuse me you're gonna have to
必须原谅我，你将不得不
stand up the history status board you're
站起来你的历史状态板
gonna have to within the history
将不得不在历史中
dashboard you're gonna have to go enter
您将必须进入的仪表板
a URL for the stream of metrics you want
您想要的指标流的URL
to look at if you want to you know look
看你是否想知道
at metrics across multiple services now
现在以多种服务的指标
you got multiple streams you're gonna
你有多个流，你要
have to go stand up turbine to do that
必须站起来涡轮才能做到这一点
and enter that turbine URL with spring
然后用spring输入该涡轮URL
cloud services you don't have to do that
云服务，您不必这样做
sprinkle out services the turbine bid is
向涡轮机投标提供服务
handled for you through this queue you
通过这个队列为您处理
basically don't even have to go in there
基本上甚至不需要去那里
and inner URL for it it's just it's
它的内部URL就是
bound
界
everything's bound up appropriately so
一切都捆绑在一起，所以
when you go into this tricks dashboard
当您进入此技巧仪表板时
you see the metrics directly you don't
您直接看到指标，而没有
have to go enter a URL or anything okay
必须输入网址或其他任何内容
I forgot about this slide yeah so this
我忘了这张幻灯片
service does have one additional wrinkle
服务确实有额外的皱纹
so like we said when you bind to a
就像我们说的那样，当您绑定到
circuit breaker dashboard service what
断路器仪表板服务什么
your app is actually getting is a rabbit
您的应用程序实际上是一只兔子
cue that it could start putting metrics
提示它可能开始放置指标
on and of course not putting metrics on
并当然不采用指标
the queue isn't something your app is
队列不是您的应用程序
doing explicitly you're including one
明确地做你包括一个
annotation that says this is a historic
说明这是历史性的注释
skom and and then every time that method
skom，然后每次使用该方法
is hit this the metrics are
被击中的指标是
automatically getting put on the queue
自动进入队列
for you so if you don't use rabbit in
为了你，所以如果你不使用兔子
your application for any messaging
您的应用程序进行任何消息传递
already really all you do is include the
实际上，您要做的只是包括
starter you get that rabbit connection
入门者，您获得了兔子连接
behind the scenes you don't even know
在幕后你甚至都不知道
it's there but the historic sin fruss
在那儿，但是历史上的罪过
truck sure knows it's there and start
卡车肯定知道它在那里并开始
standing stuff to it but what if you are
常设的东西，但如果你是
using rabbit and you
用兔子和你
application now you're gonna have to
应用程序，您现在必须
connection factorize the one we're
连接将我们分解为一个
creating behind the scenes for the
在幕后创造
history data to use and the other one
要使用的历史数据和另一个
that your client application is using in
您的客户端应用程序正在使用的
that scenario you have to do a little
这种情况下，您需要做一点
bit of coding because we have to
一点编码，因为我们必须
connection factory beans and we need to
连接工厂bean，我们需要
know which one is for which so in that
知道那个是为了那个
scenario you'd add this little bit of
场景中，您需要添加
code on top which is just annotating the
上面的代码只是注释了
connection that we're getting for
我们正在寻求的联系
history with this at Harris hystrix
哈里斯hystrix的历史
connection factory annotation and that
连接工厂注释和那个
just tells the historic syn fruss truck
只是告诉历史悠久的syn fruss卡车
sure this is the rabbit connection I
确定这是兔子的连接
want you to use and then in your own
希望您使用，然后自己使用
client code you could use something like
客户代码，您可以使用类似
an app primary annotation and then that
应用主要注释，然后
connection factory is going to get auto
连接工厂将自动
wired into all of your spring AMQP
接线到您的所有 Spring AMQP 中
infrastructure or whatever it is you're
基础设施或它是什么
using if you're using three different
如果您使用的是三种不同的
spring a and PP connections internally
内部弹簧a和PP连接
then you might have other qualifier
那么你可能还有其他资格赛
annotations on the bottom that's kind of
底部的注释
how you design it the important part is
您如何设计它的重要部分是
you can use this historic connection
您可以使用此历史连接
factory annotation to tell the hit ryx
工厂注释告诉命中的ryx
infrastructure this is the one you want
基础设施，这就是你想要的
to use and behind that call to
使用和背后的呼吁
connection factory hystrix connection
连接工厂hystrix连接
factory our code is going out finding
工厂我们的代码正在寻找
out that there is a circuit breaker
外面有一个断路器
service bound to your application
服务绑定到您的应用程序
getting all the rabbit credentials from
从所有兔子凭证
that and creating that connection
并创建该连接
factory well I'm going to ask a dumb
工厂好，我要问一个哑巴
question and no I'm not gonna ask you
问题，不，我不会问你
how it works well I am but not I'm not
我是如何运作的，但不是
expecting a magic answer this is a
期待一个神奇的答案，这是一个
serious question it's question I
严重的问题，这是我的问题
probably should have asked before we got
大概应该在我们问到之前
up here but I'm sure everybody else
在这里，但我敢肯定其他人
might one of it might want to know this
可能其中之一可能想知道这一点
I'd have the answer yeah well you might
我会回答的，是的，你可能会
know this history connection Factory and
知道这个历史联系工厂
am I would I be mistaken to say that
是我会被误认为
that's just a qualifier annotation it is
那只是一个限定词注解
just a qualifier annotation that's what
只是一个限定词注解
I figured it was so it's it's basically
我想是这样，基本上
a an annotation that is itself annotated
本身已注释的注释
with qualifier and then internally
与预选赛，然后在内部
within spring cloud services we're
在春季云服务中，我们
looking for that specific qualification
寻找那个特定的资格
that specific qualifier when it comes
那个特定的限定词
time to pick this that's so it's we're
是时候选择这个了，所以我们
basically doing the same thing you would
基本上做你会做的同样的事情
do in spring if you have multiple rabbit
如果你有多只兔子，在春季做
rabbit beans to work with we were
兔子 bean 一起工作
qualifying one it's a history connection
限定一个是历史联系
factory I'm glad I knew the answer for
工厂很高兴我知道答案
that question I was nervous I thought
我以为那个问题我很紧张
that was the answer but I wasn't sure
那是答案，但我不确定
okay and I see the circuit breaker
好吧，我看到断路器
circuit breaker is fine so we had a
断路器很好，所以我们有一个
break stuff I mean it's in the name
打破东西，我的意思是它的名字
circuit
电路
let's see how see how this will work all
让我们看看如何看到这将如何工作
right so I'll show you the code first
对，所以我先给你看代码
since we're here to go see if I know
因为我们在这里去看看我是否知道
where to find it out believe it'll be in
在哪里找到它相信它会在
here Oh actually I believe it's not in
哦，实际上我相信它不在
here where did I put this or where did
在这里我把它放在哪里或在哪里
Matt put this more accurate in the UI
马特（Matt）在界面中更准确地说明了这一点
right it's in the UI no wonder I'm lost
对，它在用户界面中，难怪我迷路了
okay circuit breaker is always from the
好的断路器总是从
perspective of the caller so the caller
呼叫者的视角，所以呼叫者
is the one that's got the
是有的
instrumentation saying I'm in this case
仪器说我在这种情况下
the UI I'm trying to call the server are
我试图调用服务器的用户界面是
those calls working or not and if those
那些电话工作与否，如果那些
calls start to fail from the caller's
从呼叫者的呼叫开始失败
perspective then that's really what we
角度来看，那真的是我们
want to know about yeah so what we have
想知道是的，所以我们有
here is we have this one method called
这是我们有一种称为
random fortune it's going to be called
随机的财富将被称为
from the controller so it can serve up a
从控制器，以便它可以服务
fortune and it's gonna simply use rest
财富，它会简单地利用休息
template to do a get for object and
模板来获取对象和
notice the URL there I mean it says
注意那里的URL，我的意思是说
nothing - a circuit breaker but it's
没什么-断路器，但是
worth mentioning it's going at the
值得一提的是它正在
service registry and looking up a
服务注册表并查找
service by the name fortunes and so you
以财富为名的服务，所以您
know if you if you put in your browser
知道是否放入浏览器
right now HTTP colon slash slash
现在HTTP冒号斜杠
fortunes it's not gonna work all that
运气不会那么好
well you can try it with curl same
好吧，你可以尝试卷曲相同
effect in fact if you were even logged
实际上，即使您已登录
into the VPN and doing the same thing
进入VPN并做同样的事情
that we're doing here you still wouldn't
我们在这里做，你还是不会
find fortunes because there is no
找到财富，因为没有
machine whose name is fortunes it's
机器的名字就是运气
using this name under the covers it's
在封面下使用此名称
using some trickery to go say hey go
用一些诡计去说嘿
find me the service name fortunes and
找到我的服务名称财富
then essentially it rewrites this URL
然后本质上它将重写此URL
before actually sending the request but
在实际发送请求之前，但是
if it works great
如果效果很好
we're gonna get a fortune back working
我们将重新获得财富
at some random for some random fortune
为了一些随机的财富
from that service if it doesn't work
从该服务，如果它不起作用
however if things are flaky let's just
但是，如果情况不佳，就让我们
say the service just went away which is
说服务刚刚消失了
an entirely possible scenario that's aa
一个完全可能的情况是
batterie have come write better yeah you
电池来了，写得更好，是的，你
come right back within that in the
马上回到里面
meantime or if you really like not only
同时或如果您真的很喜欢
removed it somebody I mean you know they
删除某人我是说你知道他们
killed it you removed it you blasted it
杀死它，将其删除，将其炸开
away or it's it for some reason
离开或由于某种原因
otherwise unhealthy maybe this thing
否则可能不健康
starts throwing an exception
开始引发异常
I don't whatever reason this is not
我不知道这不是什么原因
working if that were the case we don't
如果那不是我们的工作
want the application to fall over
希望应用程序崩溃
because some service down here is
因为这里的一些服务是
failing we don't want a cascading
失败了，我们不想级联
failure to bring the whole thing down
未能使整个事情失败
we'd like to have some nice easy way of
我们希望有一些不错的简便方法
telling people
告诉别人
hold on maybe things aren't going so
坚持下去，也许事情不会这样
well right now come back ask later kind
好吧，现在回来再问一下好吗
of thing so that's in the case of the
的东西，所以在
fortune-teller service that's what's
算命服务是什么
going on and here we've annotated it
继续，我们在这里注释了它
with history command and history command
与历史命令和历史命令
basically is telling it this could go
基本上是说这可能
wrong and when it does go wrong I want
错了，什么时候错了我想要
you to turn around and call fallback
你转身回叫
fortune instead which is this method
运气是这种方法
down here
在这里
the main rule between a history fallback
历史回退之间的主要规则
method is it has to have the same
方法是必须具有相同的
signature as the method that it's
签名作为它的方法
falling back for which is pretty easy
退回这很容易
when you don't take any parameters but
当你不带任何参数但是
if this were to fail for any reason this
如果由于任何原因失败
gets called as soon as it becomes
成为后立即被调用
healthy again it goes back to doing what
再次恢复健康
it was doing before so and this is also
之前是这样做的，这也是
where the metrics come from so this at
指标来自何处
hysterics command which is a part of
属于迟滞的命令
screen cloud right worse the fact that
屏幕云对更糟的事实是
you have that on there also means every
你在那里那里也意味着每个
time this method gets called some
这个方法被称为
metrics are going to be captured and
指标将被捕获，
sent off to this RabbitMQ which goes to
发送到该RabbitMQ，
turbine which then goes to the dashboard
涡轮，然后转到仪表板
indeed so here we are we're back at the
的确如此，我们回到了
app I'm just gonna show you it working a
应用程序，我只是向您展示它的工作原理
few a few more times hopefully it works
希望再过几次
yeah I think fear has hurt me but we'll
是的，我认为恐惧伤害了我，但我们会
see yeah your shoes my shoes are not
看，你的鞋子我的鞋子不是
making me happy today I these are not
今天让我开心，我不是
comfortable at all so tell you what
舒服一点，告诉你什么
we're gonna do we're gonna kind of come
我们要去，我们要来
over here and where we have were at the
在这里，我们曾经在
UI I want to go to I want to go to this
我要转到的用户界面我要转到的用户界面
house if I'm in the right spot I want to
房子，如果我在正确的位置，我想
go to the service and I'm just gonna
去服务，我会
kill the service understand purposefully
故意终止服务
bring it down
拿下来
sure let's stop that so there is no
当然，让我们停止吧，所以没有
furch in service it's gone I come back
在服务中走了，我回来了
over here to the app I hit refresh your
在这里点击我要刷新的应用
future is unclear because what happens
未来尚不清楚，因为会发生什么
and we tried to make that request there
我们试图在那里提出要求
was no service to be to be found it it
没有被发现的服务
tried to make the caller couldn't find
试图使呼叫者找不到
the service failed something went wrong
服务失败，出了点问题
history command caught it turned it
历史命令抓住了它
around and sent it to the the fallback
并将其发送给后备
method and so I can keep doing this all
方法，所以我可以继续做这一切
day long and until that service comes
整天，直到该服务到来
back my future is gonna be unclear I'll
回到我的未来会变得模糊我会
bring the service back but before I do
把服务带回来，但是在我做之前
let me let me go over here I got to show
让我让我过去在这里我必须证明
you the history dashboard and the
您的历史记录仪表板和
easiest way to get to that
最简单的方法
is to come over here find the yeah find
是要过来找耶
the co the circuit breaker do manage
断路器共同管理
wait for it and here we have the circuit
等待它，这里我们有电路
breaker dashboard now we only have that
断路器仪表板现在我们只有
one circuit breaker so it's not terribly
一个断路器，所以不是很困难
interesting at the moment but I'll see
目前很有趣，但我会看到
if I can add some life to it a totally
如果我能给它增加一些生命的话
wrong window this is the one I want it
错误的窗口，这是我想要的窗口
alright see if I get some life to it by
好吧，看看我是否有生命
just hitting refresh on this a few times
只是几次刷新
and you can see it's actually doing
你可以看到它实际上在做
something right now that little ball
现在那个小球
turned red because it's it's unhealthy
变红是因为它不健康
at the moment and see how two percent
此刻，看看百分之二
failure rate over there on the right
右边那边的故障率
yeah percent failure is pretty pretty
是的，失败的百分比非常漂亮
high at the moment I would say things
此刻我会高谈阔论
are not good at much higher than a
不擅长于
hundred percent oh yeah
百分百哦耶
yeah if you have a hundred and ten
是的，如果你有一百零一
percent failure you're really in trouble
失败百分比，您确实遇到了麻烦
let's see if I can find my window that I
让我们看看是否可以找到我的窗口
drug away where I'm blue that's good
药物消失在我忧郁的地方，那很好
let's go back to I see if I can bring
回去看看我是否可以带
that that fortune service back up and
那个财富服务备份了，
get things back in business now it takes
现在就让事情恢复正常
a moment or two for this thing just not
一两分钟的事情就是
only start but also for it to tell
只是开始但也要告诉
Eureka that it's back in business and so
尤里卡（Eureka），它重新营业了，所以
this is not gonna work through that
这不会通过那工作
Alegria dashboard right I'm sorry we
Alegria仪表板正确，我们很抱歉
could see that we could see that in the
可以看到，我们可以看到
Eureka dashboard but we did not the
尤里卡仪表板，但我们没有
keynote the other night so yeah so I'm
前一天的主题演讲，是的，所以我
just gonna hit refresh here for a little
会在这里刷新一下
while while we waiting for things to get
而当我们等待事情得到
better
更好
and like I said it may take there we go
就像我说的那样，我们可能要去那里
it looks like it's back and notice I'm
看起来又回来了，注意到我
starting to get my failure rates going
开始让我的失败率上升
down I'm starting to see more green
下来我开始看到更多的绿色
numbers over here in the history
历史上这里的数字
dashboard so things are healthy now but
仪表板，所以现在情况很健康，但是
I didn't have to like I would normally
我不必像往常一样
would have to do with history I didn't
与我没有的历史有关
have to go in and tell it where that's
必须进去告诉它在哪里
where that stream of metrics was it's
指标流在哪里
just because it's bound because the
只是因为它的绑定，因为
history dashboard is bound to our
历史记录仪表板已绑定到我们
application it's just going to know
应用程序，它只是要知道
where to get that it those metrics from
从哪里获得这些指标
and under the covers as Scott mentioned
并在斯科特提到的掩护下
it's via that message broker all right
是通过那个消息代理的
wrong ones like about it doesn't it
像这样的错人不是吗
well these services we've talked about
这些我们已经讨论过的服务
all three of them so that's what we came
他们三个人，所以我们来了
to tell you about today this is
告诉你今天是
available on pivotal Cloud Foundry in
在以下关键性Cloud Foundry中可用
beta form today it'll be available you
Beta版今天将可用
know one dot ODG a very soon and at some
很快就知道一个点ODG
point later in the year on pivotal web
在今年晚些时候在关键网络上指向
services so what questions do we have
服务，所以我们有什么问题
now is a great time for some questions
现在是一些问题的好时机
or some answers if you have any yes
或一些答案（如果有）
the a property from the config server
配置服务器中的属性
within the app itself actually I don't
在应用程序本身中实际上我不
know Matt is there does the app itself
知道Matt有应用程式本身吗
show any properties from the config from
显示来自配置的任何属性
the config server I don't think so it's
我不认为的配置服务器
all like Eureka completely yeah yeah it
完全像尤里卡一样
doesn't I mean it could and you could
我不是说可以，你可以
use like a configuration properties
像配置属性一样使用
annotation from spring boot to inject it
从Spring Boot注解以注入它
into a property just like you would any
就像您一样
other property but as it's written now
其他财产，但现在写的
it does not any other question there we
那里没有其他问题了
go
走
so the question is how does essentially
所以问题是本质上如何
the question is how does Eureka know
问题是尤里卡怎么知道
that that service has been reinstated so
该服务已恢复，因此
that when I am making that call or I
当我打电话或我
guess how does Mike my client my my
猜猜我的客户迈克怎么样
service registry client know that that
服务注册表客户端知道
service is now healthy again and
服务现在又健康了，
therefore I can start I can continue
因此，我可以开始，我可以继续
making calls instead of going to the
拨打电话而不是去
fallback method and you know what I have
后备方法，你知道我有什么
a theory on how that works but I
关于它如何工作的理论，但是我
honestly I've never actually given it
老实说我从来没有真正给过它
much thought do you happen to know
你好想知道
well the circuit breaker like that
像这样的断路器
hystrix command there's no sort of
hystrix命令没有任何种类的
artificial calls being made to that
对此人为地打电话
service being called all history is
被称为所有历史的服务是
doing is measuring of all the calls that
就是测量所有的呼叫
are made from the caller side how many
从来电者方取得了多少
are succeeding and how many are failing
成功，有多少失败
so there's no sort of heartbeat going to
所以没有任何心跳
it or anything it's just capturing the
它或任何它只是捕获
metrics from the actual calls from in
来自的实际调用的指标
this case the UI to the service yeah but
这种情况下服务的用户界面是的，但是
how does it know yeah that's that's
它怎么知道是的
about what I believe to be the cases it
关于我认为是这样的情况
tries every now and again but I wasn't
尝试一次又一次，但我不是
going to answer that without knowing for
会不知不觉地回答
sure yeah yeah I'm sorry I misunderstood
可以，对不起，我误会了
yeah there's an algorithm inside of
是的，里面有一个算法
history that figures that out and if you
历史可以弄清楚，如果你
go out to the netflix history
走出netflix的历史
documentation it'll document what that
记录它会记录什么
algorithm is to figure out if it's down
算法是找出是否下降
how many of the tries it actually tries
它实际尝试了多少次尝试
to send again versus how many it just
再次发送与发送多少
automatically short circuits or open
自动短路或开路
circuits yeah so you can get the details
是的，所以您可以获得详细信息
there on what that algorithm is and how
关于那个算法是什么以及如何
you can configure in tune that algorithm
您可以调整该算法
yeah there's a lot of properties you can
是的，有很多属性可以
configure Eureka with probably more than
配置Eureka可能不止
you'd ever care to know but that's that
你曾经想知道，但是那是
that historic stew one of them yeah yeah
那个历史悠久的炖菜之一，是的，是的
say yeah same thing with history and
对历史说同样的话，
configure Exeter degree yes
配置埃克塞特学位是
how does how does it know these yeah the
怎么知道这些呢
question is how does this work if you're
问题是，如果您是
not writing a Java app to run as a
不编写Java应用程序以
server but it's iOS or Android or mobile
服务器，但它是iOS或Android或移动设备
yeah what you're gonna do there is
是的，你要做的是
you're not going to hit any of these
你不会碰到这些
services directly from a mobile client
直接从移动客户端提供服务
whether it be JavaScript or Android or
无论是JavaScript还是Android，还是
iOS or anything like that you're not
iOS或类似的东西
gonna hit those services directly
会直接打那些服务
because you got it never mind security
因为你懂了安全
you have a hold another problem before
你之前还有另一个问题
that you got to figure out where they
你要弄清楚他们在哪里
are you don't even know where the URL is
你甚至不知道URL在哪里
for them and so it's not part of spring
对他们来说，所以这不是春天的一部分
cloud services that we have that's where
我们拥有的云服务就是
Zul comes in and so Zul can capture one
祖尔进来，所以祖尔可以捕获一个
or more other services and proxy to them
或更多其他服务并代理给他们
through a single single API URL and so
通过单个API URL等等
it's at its through that same API URL
通过相同的API URL
that you can also do security and that
您还可以进行安全保护，
can be oh oh off it can be basic off
可以哦哦可以关闭它可以基本关闭
whatever you deem appropriate for your
任何您认为适合您的
app and the client can deal with it just
应用程序，客户端可以处理它
like it would any other if it was a
就像其他任何东西一样
single API I do believe it just kind of
单个API，我相信它只是一种
plug an article I didn't write the
插入我没有写的文章
article but dr. Davis I wrote a
文章，但博士。戴维斯我写了
excellent series of articles on the
优秀的系列文章
spring blog over the last several months
最近几个月的The Spring Blog
and he goes into exactly that's that
他进入那就是
scenario how do you write a client hit
场景如何编写客户匹配
in his case it wasn't like an Android or
在他的情况下，它不像是Android或
iOS it was angular if I remember right
如果我没记错的话，iOS是有角度的
but an angular client consuming services
但是有角度的客户会使用服务
that are secured and he's doing it right
是安全的，他做对了
through Zul yes
通过祖尔
I wasn't hearing that what I'm not sure
我没听到我不确定
I caught the question yeah
我抓住了这个问题
is there a specific model that's used by
有没有使用特定的模型
a config server it's not the question
配置服务器，这不是问题
security model would we expose the
安全模型，我们将揭露
security model outside of
外部的安全模型
well I mean the whole idea I don't know
好吧，我的意思是我不知道的整个想法
the answer I can't say definitively S or
我不能说肯定的答案S或
no on that but my knee-jerk reaction is
不，但是我的下意识反应是
to say no the whole point of that is we
并不是说我们的全部意思是
don't want anyone to consume that config
不想让任何人使用该配置
server unless they are bound to it they
服务器，除非他们绑定到它
don't we don't mean in theory I suppose
我想我们不是在理论上讲的意思吗
that would be a nice thing you could do
那可以做的很好
is you could just say hey here's
你能说嘿吗
configuration everybody come you know
配置大家来你知道
and get it but we're thinking of more of
并得到它，但我们正在考虑更多
an cloud native enterprise type
云原生企业类型
application where you really don't want
您真正不想要的应用程序
that you want the configuration private
您想要私有的配置
and only available to those those
并且仅适用于那些
services that are actually bound to the
实际绑定到
configuration server and so it doesn't
配置服务器，所以它没有
make a whole lot of sense to expose that
揭露那个很有意义
outside but once they're bound to it
在外面，但一旦他们被绑定
it's piece of cake
这是小菜一碟
I mean we automatically as you've seen I
我的意思是我们就像您看到的那样自动
mean there's no code we wrote in the in
表示我们在中没有编写任何代码
the fortune teller app there was no code
算命应用程序没有代码
written to actually go negotiate that
书面去实际谈判
security to get to those properties it
获得这些属性的安全性
just it just works you could certainly
只是它可以工作，你当然可以
go you know dig into the property's
去你知道挖财产的
yourself and do it yourself if you
自己做，如果你自己做
wanted to but I can I can think of no
想，但我能想到没有
reason why we would ever want to
为什么我们会想要
necessarily expose that outside of to
必然暴露给
anything that's not bound to the config
任何未绑定到配置的内容
server directly
直接服务器
how would you secure this outside of
您如何将其固定在
cloud bound you would well what you you
云绑定你会好你自己
would do what we did you just do it
会做我们刚才做的事
yourself
你自己
write the same code we did but using
编写与我们相同的代码，但使用
right at yourself you'd use spring
对自己，你会用弹簧
security spring security for a lot yeah
安全Spring Security 很多
this is a good time to to plug the one
这是插入一个的好时机
talk we were gonna want to plug is the
我们要塞的话题是
way that we did all of this security was
我们完成所有这些安全措施的方式是
spring security OAuth that is some
Spring Security OAuth这是一些
fairly complicated stuff to get you head
相当复杂的东西让你头脑清醒
around and use there's another talk
周围和使用还有另一个话题
tomorrow afternoon that is this security
明天下午就是这个安全
micro services with spring cloud
带有Spring Cloud的微服务
security that talk is by will Tran who's
谈话的安全是由Tran谁
on our team
在我们的团队中
and helped us implement a lot of this
并帮助我们实现了很多
security he's not going to talk about
他不会谈论的安全性
our code but he's going to talk about
我们的代码，但他将要谈论
all exactly the same tools and
所有完全相同的工具，
techniques we used in our code in some
我们在某些代码中使用的技术
other sample apps that he's got so if
他拥有的其他示例应用程序，如果
you're interested in how that oauth2
您对那个oauth2感兴趣
stuff works and how to write spring apps
东西有效，以及如何编写Spring应用程序
that do the same things we did you
做和我们一样的事情
should definitely go to that talk and
应该去参加那个演讲，
he'll answer all those questions better
他会更好地回答所有这些问题
than we can appear yes
比我们可以出现的
yeah all the historic s-- metrics are
是的，所有历史性指标
gonna say is did this call work or did
会说这个电话是工作还是做
it not work from there hopefully you're
从那里不能工作希望你在
getting some logs from one side or the
从一侧或其他获取一些日志
other that you can go inspect logs for
其他的你可以去检查日志
those applications and try to figure out
这些应用程序并尝试找出
okay it's working I'm getting some
好吧，它正在工作，我得到一些
failures there not enough failures that
失败没有足够的失败
the circuit is opening but I'm getting
电路开了，但我越来越
some failures and what am I seeing in
一些失败，我看到了什么
logs it's only when I'm passing this
仅在我通过时记录
parameter that I'm getting a failure or
我失败的参数或
some condition like that well the yeah
像那样的状况很好
it's it's it's the circuit breaker is on
这是断路器已打开
a given well the the metrics you're
给定的指标是
seeing is on a given circuit breaker not
看到不在给定的断路器上
on a given service so there could be
在给定的服务上，所以可能会有
multiple circuit breakers within that
里面的多个断路器
service but if you have multiple
服务，但如果您有多个
instances of service which circuit
服务实例哪个电路
breaker is it reporting on and you gotta
断路器正在报告，您必须
remember the circuit breaker is always
记住断路器总是
from the caller side right well the
从来电者的角度来看
circuit breaker is recording is the call
断路器正在录音
are able to talk to this thing or not
能跟这个东西说话
it's not reporting what's going on on
它没有报告正在发生的事情
the back in denied all it knows is it
后面否认所有它知道的是
didn't work or not yeah that's all it
没用，是的，仅此而已
knows and at that point if you start
知道，到那时，如果您开始
seeing you know failures like if you
看到你知道失败，就像你
have five service five instances and and
有五个服务五个实例，并且
like 20% of them seem to be failing that
好像有20％的人认为
means one of them is is probably dead
意味着其中一个可能已经死了
now it's you need to go a little deeper
现在，您需要更深入一点
in the dashboards not gonna help you
在仪表板上不会帮助您
figure that out but you can go a little
弄清楚，但你可以走一点
deeper look at the logs for some of
更深入地查看一些日志
those services and and maybe do some of
这些服务，也许做一些
this you know we talked a little bit
这个你知道我们聊了一点
about tracing in the keynote last night
关于昨晚主题演讲中的追踪
some of that tracing might give you some
某些跟踪可能会给您一些
of that information as well it's not
这些信息也不是
something we are offering at Spring
我们在春季提供的东西
cloud services currently but circuit
云服务，但电路
breaker could help you see that some
断路器可以帮助您看到一些
percentage of those calls are failing
这些呼叫的百分比失败
what's going on on that back end you're
那个后端发生了什么
gonna have to start digging into that
必须开始深入研究
service and what's going on with it
服务以及它发生了什么
yeah we had a question over here
是的，我们在这里有一个问题
he's eagerly asked raising his hand can
他急切地要求举手
this be done on a private cloud pivotal
这可以在关键的私有云上​​完成
Cloud Foundry is basically pivotal
Cloud Foundry基本上是至关重要的
implementation in Cloud Foundry that
在Cloud Foundry中实施
runs on private cloud right so you can
在私有云上运行，因此您可以
install pivotal cloud foundry on vSphere
在vSphere上安装关键的Cloud Foundry
on OpenStack you can install it on AWS
在OpenStack上，您可以在AWS上安装它
if you get through that private cloud if
如果您通过该私有云，
you have your own AWS so you can install
您拥有自己的AWS，因此可以安装
pivotal Cloud Foundry on any of those
任何这些方面的关键Cloud Foundry
and then you can install spring CLOB
然后您可以安装spring CLOB
services on top of that right and
在此之上的服务以及
there's a guy back here we'll be happy
有一个男人回到这里，我们会很高兴
to sell you that I mean essentially red
卖给你，我的意思是本质上是红色
and blue that I was showing you those
和蓝色，我向你展示了那些
are private clouds
是私有云
well yeah but conceptually it's the you
是的，但是从概念上讲是你
know as far as the network topology is
了解网络拓扑
concerned it's it would be very little
担心会很少
different than what you would have is a
与您所拥有的不同的是
internal private cloud versus a just
内部私有云与公正
some a test environment I have that's
我有一些测试环境
also behind the firewall yes
也在防火墙后面
I'm sorry I couldn't make that out
对不起，我不能说清楚
basically what are the conditions that a
基本上是什么条件
circuit breaker would be considered to
断路器将被认为是
fail the most obvious one is infant
失败最明显的是婴儿
exceptions throughout but there's other
整个例外，但还有其他
scenarios such as if it's being slow to
场景，如它正在缓慢
respond and there's configuration you
回应，你有配置
can put in there to say hey if it hasn't
可以放那里说嘿，如果没有
if it's you know being kind of sluggish
如果你知道自己有点迟钝
maybe it hasn't reached some you know
也许还没有达到你所知道的
some threshold of response time then
某个响应时间阈值
that's considered also a failure but the
这也被认为是失败的，但是
easy the easy one to talk about is if
容易容易谈论的是
exceptions throw exceptions thrown that
抛出异常抛出异常
that broke therefore fall back and do
坏了，因此退后并做
something else okay
还可以
I don't believe if the service returns a
我不相信该服务是否返回
specific value I don't believe you can
具体的价值我不相信你可以
although well you can you just have to
虽然好，您可以只需要
write some code around it where you
在它周围写一些代码
yourself are saying if this happens
你自己在说这是否发生
throw an exception if not don't but it's
抛出异常（如果不是），但是
not really that's not the intent because
这不是真的不是因为
the circuit breaker is more about the
断路器更多的是关于
the health of a service not necessarily
服务的健康状况不一定
what the service is serving and I mean
服务正在服务什么，我的意思是
certainly you could say you know you
当然你可以说你知道你
make the call and if they return
打电话，如果他们回来
something you don't like throw an
你不喜欢的东西
exception which would then make a
例外，然后将
fallback happen you could do that that's
发生后备情况，您可以那样做
just not really what it's intended for
只是不是真正的目的
yes
是
yeah so you'd like to you know certain
是的，所以您想知道
failures to not necessarily be failures
失败不一定是失败
you would like them to not necessarily
您希望他们不一定
retry in those cases like if the network
在某些情况下重试，例如网络
we're down you wouldn't want to keep
我们很沮丧，你不想保留
retrying knowing the network's now
重试了解现在的网络
actually I'm not sure why you wouldn't
其实我不确定为什么你不会
want to do that if networks down it
想在网络中断的情况下这样做
still gonna fall back and eventually the
仍然会退后，最终
network will come back
网络将会回来
oh can you define a distinct called a
哦，您可以定义一个独特的名称吗
fallback behavior depending on what the
后备行为取决于
failure was good question you know i
失败是个好问题，你知道我
honestly don't know yeah that would
老实说不知道是的
again be district's open-source project
再次成为学区的开源项目
and we have to research what its
我们必须研究它的
capabilities are in that regard yeah one
在这方面的能力是的
thing I sort of as you were asking this
我有点像你问的那样
I thought you were asking a different
我以为你在问另外一个
question so I'm gonna answer the
问题，所以我要回答
question I thought you were asking
我以为你在问的问题
though and that is with a fortune-teller
虽然，那是一个算命先生
you a application it's really a nice
您一个应用程序真的很棒
simple application that's one of the
简单的应用程序是
beauties of it is it's it's simple
它的美是它很简单
enough you can kind of get your head
够你可以让你的头
around all the pieces pretty easily
轻松地围绕所有碎片
because there's only two and in a
因为只有两个
typical micro-services architecture you
典型的微服务架构
wouldn't necessarily add that UI that'd
不一定会添加该用户界面
be the only place where you would have
是您唯一拥有的地方
circuit breakers you you know that might
您知道的断路器可能
call a service which calls another
呼叫另一个服务
service which calls another service
调用另一个服务的服务
which calls another service you don't
哪个叫你不叫的服务
know how deep this goes
知道这有多深
but at all levels you could have circuit
但在所有级别上您都可以拥有电路
breakers and so failures and fall backs
破坏者等失败和后退
could happen anywhere in the application
可能在应用程序中的任何地方发生
and kind of the the general rule of
和一般的规则
thumb I've heard two different people
拇指我听过两个不同的人
say this so I can't I don't know who to
说这个，所以我不知道该向谁
give the quote to the general rule of
引述一般原则
thumb is where do I where do you play
拇指是我在哪里玩
circuit breakers you place them where
断路器，您将其放置在
things might go wrong yeah and so it
事情可能会出错，是的，所以
could be anywhere in the app and in most
可以在应用程序中的任何位置，并且在大多数情况下
of these sample apps what you'll usually
这些示例应用程序中，通常会用到什么
see also is you try to call some
另请参阅您是否尝试拨打一些电话
external service through rest template
通过rest模板进行外部服务
and if it doesn't work you have some
如果不起作用，您有一些
hard-coded value that's the easiest
最简单的硬编码值
example but you might have in a real
例子，但是你可能有一个真实的
world case as you try to call one
尝试呼叫一个世界案例
service and if you start seeing failures
服务，如果您开始看到故障
you might call some backup service that
您可能会致电一些备份服务
is maybe an older version with less
可能是旧版本，而更少
functionality but you want to give it a
功能，但您想给它一个
shot and if that doesn't work then the
射击，如果那不起作用，那么
third step is you return some empty
第三步，你返回一些空
value or some hard-coded value that
值或一些硬编码的值
things can consume so you can stack them
东西会消耗掉，所以你可以堆叠它们
deeper that way as well right what else
这样更深，还有其他
here's one
这是一个
every time with the configuration
每次配置
repository I couldn't hear you terribly
我听不到你的声音
well but yeah configuration repository
很好，但是配置库
how would you deal with dead verses QA
您将如何处理死经质量检查
versus production would you have a
与生产相比，您有
different repository would you have the
您有不同的存储库
same repository is that the question
同一存储库是那个问题
it depends what do you want to do I mean
这取决于你想做什么
in theory they could be the same
理论上它们可能是相同的
repository but they're probably not
仓库，但可能不是
because you probably don't want to have
因为你可能不想
production properties in your repository
存储库中的生产属性
that your dev and QA teams are also
您的开发人员和质量检查团队也
hitting depends on depends on the nature
击球取决于性质
of the properties in some cases it may
在某些情况下可能会
not matter it could be different
没关系，可能会有所不同
branches in the same repo that's what I
我在同一仓库中分支
was thinking is in that case you
当时在想你
probably want to go with branches or
可能想和树枝一起去
somewhere you know something along those
在某个地方你知道那些东西
lines and maybe you know there's all
行，也许你知道所有的一切
sorts of different scenarios just as
各种不同的情况就像
just as there are different ways of
就像有不同的方式
migrating your code through through a
通过一个迁移您的代码
repository and different and branches
仓库和不同和分支
and and and whatnot the same thing would
和和什么不一样的东西会
apply here so one one scenario that I
在这里申请，这样一种情况，我
thought of while standing here answering
想到站在这里接听
this is you could have in your branch a
这是你可以在你的分支
dev conceived config but in your master
开发人员构思了配置，但在您的主服务器中
its production if at any point you
它的生产，如果你在任何时候
needed to merge that in you could you
需要将其合并到您体内
just of course you need to take care not
当然，您需要注意不要
to merge things that are sensitive from
合并敏感的东西
dev or that might break production but
开发人员或可能会中断生产，但
still you you could do that same kind of
仍然你可以做同样的事情
thing you could have multiple paths
你可能有多个路径
so you could say slash production is
所以你可以说斜线生产是
production convict's and slash dava's
生产罪犯和斜杠dava
dev configs I mean there's a lot of
开发配置，我的意思是有很多
scenarios kind of just depends on what
情况只是取决于什么
seems most appropriate for you or you
似乎最适合您
could do it the good old-fashioned way
可以用老式的方式做到
and just have distinct repositories for
只是有不同的存储库
each one yeah
每一个人
no absolutely not would it be a bad
不，绝对不会是一件坏事
practice to have a macro service called
练习拥有一个称为的宏服务
another macro service very good practice
另一个宏服务非常好的做法
it's in fact you saw this happening he
事实上，你看到了这种情况，他
wasn't obvious but it was in fact
并不明显，但实际上
happening because both the both the
之所以发生，是因为两者
fortune-teller service and the
算命服务和
fortune-teller your eye both called out
算命先生你的眼睛都喊出来了
to another macro service the service
到另一个宏服务的服务
being config sever and the service being
正在配置服务器，服务正在
service registry
服务注册表
so so you're worried about you're
所以你担心自己
worried about testing so when you're
担心测试，所以当你
testing micro-service one you're also
测试微服务，您也是
indirectly testing two well certainly if
间接测试两个肯定是否
they are deployed in the cloud as you've
将它们部署到云中
described yeah that would be the side
描述是的那是一面
effect of that and so your scenarios are
这样的效果，所以您的方案是
well you just accept that or you for the
好吧，你只是接受那个，或者你接受
purpose of testing bind it to a faked
测试的目的将其绑定到假冒产品
out version or something like that but
版本或类似的东西，但
the truth is I mean that's that's at a
事实是，我的意思是
more closer to production test that's
更接近生产测试
that's when you're doing more of an
那就是你要做更多的事情
integration style testing and which is a
集成样式测试，这是一个
good style of testing so in that case
良好的测试风格，在这种情况下
yes you would still want to do that but
是的，您仍然想这样做，但是
when you're when you're developing
当你在发展的时候
locally on your machine and you're
在您的计算机上本地
running the same service it's just a web
运行相同的服务，只是一个网络
app and it's making a call out to some
应用程序，它正在呼唤一些人
something and and so it there's no
东西，所以没有
reason it has to actually hit a real
为什么它必须真正击中一个真正的
service it could hit a fake service you
服务可能会打假服务
can do things like simple thing you
可以做一些简单的事情
could do is use spring MVC's test spring
可以做的就是使用Spring MVC的测试弹簧
of your spring MVC client testing that
您的Spring MVC客户端测试
was introduced in spring 3 dot something
在春天3点东西介绍
I think I forget when it was it came
我想我忘记了什么时候来的
around and then you can basically mock
周围，​​然后你基本上可以嘲笑
out the responses it's it's as if it's
出来的答案就像是
going to the to another service but it
去另一个服务，但它
never even hits the network it just
从来没有碰过网络
responds it immediately
立即回应
that's not an old pattern it's a good
这不是一个旧模式，这是一个好习惯
pattern right
模式正确
hmm
嗯
sure sure and so you're saying so you
当然可以，所以你说的是你
have a controller at calling service one
有一个呼叫服务员的控制器
service - and service one doesn't know
服务-服务不知道
about service - and that's clean the
关于服务-这很干净
same scenario could happen with micro
微型可能会发生相同的情况
services I mean it'd be nice to keep
服务我的意思是保留它会很好
those independent of each other and so
那些彼此独立的
when I say ace micro Service is calling
当我说ace micro Service打电话时
another micro service I probably don't
我可能不喜欢的另一个微服务
mean necessarily although yes you could
意味着必要，尽管是的，你可以
do this but you don't necessarily mean
这样做，但您不一定要
this one calls this this one calls this
这个叫这个这个叫这个
and then this one also calls this one I
然后这个也叫我
don't necessarily mean that it could
不一定意味着它可以
mean this you know the your app calls a
意味着您知道您的应用调用了
macro service and then that macro
宏服务，然后该宏
service calls yet another micro service
服务呼叫另一个微服务
it itself is a client for another
它本身就是另一个的客户
service because at the end of the day
服务，因为在一天结束时
your UI is itself conceptually a macro
您的UI在概念上本身就是一个宏
service it just doesn't expose like a
服务它只是不会像
REST API it exposes a human facing API
REST API，它公开了面向人类的API
in a well designed monolith you know if
在精心设计的整体中，您知道是否
you're drawing a dependency graph within
您正在绘制一个依赖图
your code you typically want that
您通常需要的代码
dependency graph to be like a tree that
依赖图就像一棵树
goes down without a bunch of spaghetti
掉下来没有一堆意大利面
lines going sideways right in micro
线在微型向右走
services it's the same thing if you've
服务，如果您有同样的事情
some layers of services you still want a
您仍然需要一些服务
nice clean dependency graph without a
不错的干净依赖图，没有
lot of spaghetti and lines of going
意大利面条和行的路线很多
sideways and things like that it doesn't
侧身，这样的事情不会
really change that so to go back to your
真正改变这一点，以便回到您的
original question you asked is it a
您问的原始问题是
considered a bad practice or I think
被认为是不好的做法，或者我认为
that's how you word it is considered a
这就是您所说的话
bad practice for one micro service to
一种微服务的不良做法
call another micro service the answer
给另一个微服务打电话答案
generally is no it's not but depends on
通常不是，不是，而是取决于
how what where they live within that
他们如何生活在那
tree of dependencies it may be
依赖树
well micro sir well I'm gonna say
好吧，先生，我要说
something and then I'm gonna take it
东西，然后我要拿它
back but just answer your question and
返回，但只需回答您的问题，
yes in a sense micro service is exposing
是的，从某种意义上说，微服务正在暴露
a REST API therefore it does have a
REST API，因此它确实有一个
controller well but micro service can
控制器很好，但微服务可以
contain business logic right indeed so
确实包含业务逻辑
don't assume that a micro service is
不要以为微服务是
only this thing that knows how to talk
只有这个会说话的东西
to a database and return data from that
到数据库并从中返回数据
you might have Micro services that kind
你可能有那种微服务
of fit that stereotype of the dao that
那个道的刻板印象
we used to talk about in the monolith
我们曾经在整体中谈论
world you may have other micro services
世界，您可能还有其他微服务
that implement some bit of business
实现一些业务
logic and have to talk to daos to go
逻辑，必须与daos交谈
grab information and process it you may
获取信息并对其进行处理
have a micro service that's a pricing
有价格的微服务
engine you may have a micro service that
引擎，您可能有一个微服务，
is going out and getting customer data
正在外出并获取客户数据
and their invoices and munging those
以及他们的发票和那些
together and doing stuff with them so in
一起和他们一起做东西
that case you might have customers as a
在这种情况下，您可能会有客户作为
micro service invoices a micro service
微服务开具微服务发票
and then a business service that's
然后是一个商业服务
calling both of those that business
称这两个生意
service is still a micro service right
服务仍然是微服务
so it's just kind of the terminology of
所以这只是...的术语
how we're plying it I think if you
我们如何努力，我想如果你
consider all those things services then
然后考虑所有这些服务
yeah they can all different services can
是的，他们可以提供所有不同的服务
call services and how you break them
呼叫服务以及如何中断它们
down I mean there's a lot of a lot of
下来，我的意思是有很多
strategies for how you divide these
您如何划分这些策略
these it really comes down to your your
这些真的取决于你
particular problem in your business but
您业务中的特殊问题，但是
for some general guidance on that I do
对于我的一些一般指导
recommend you pick up and it's an easy
建议您接机，这很容易
read you could probably read it before
读过你可能以前读过
you go to bed tonight pick up Matt
你今晚上床去接马特
Stein's migrating to cloud native or
斯坦因迁移到原生云或
Kimber what it's called migrating to
金伯所谓的迁移到
something it's about that thick it's a
大约那么厚的东西
micro book yeah it's a micro book easy
微书是的，这很容易
read and that it has some general
阅读，它有一些一般
guidance in there for that you know and
在那里的指导，您知道并且
some some of the thinking that goes into
一些想法
building these types of applications or
构建这些类型的应用程序或
you can ask him he's right there oh he's
你可以问他他就在那里哦他
gonna go sign books so go check that out
要去签名簿，所以去看看
that's not necessarily how you would
那不一定是你会的方式
break it down that's I mean that's kind
分解那是我的意思
of that even in a monolith you know UI
即使在整体中，您也知道UI
or controller and service and Dowell
或控制器和服务以及Dowell
that was just a convenient paradigm to
那只是一个方便的范例
sort of start with but it's not even
有点开始，但甚至没有
necessarily how applications ended up
必然是如何结束应用程序的
being broken down that was just a
被分解只是一个
convenient way to go to kind of start
方便的开始方式
with but a lot of times services
有很多次服务
themselves may in turn call out to other
他们自己可能反过来呼唤其他人
services if you want to call them that
服务，如果您想给他们打电话
even within a monolith because the
即使在整体中，因为
service just got too busy it had too
服务太忙了
many things going on inside of it it
它里面发生了很多事情
made sense to break into something in
闯入其中是有意义的
the multiple pieces so even on a
甚至在一个
monolith that's not necessarily where
巨石不一定在哪里
you end up at that's just maybe a good
你最终可能只是个好选择
kind of starting point when it comes to
谈到的起点
dealing with micro services you might
处理微服务，您可能会
you might think that way you might
你可能会想
continue you might start that way but
继续，你可能会这样开始，但是
the reality is you come down to dividing
现实是你会分裂
your services in two first off what
您的服务首先要两个
makes sense for your application but
对您的应用程序有意义，但
generally you think about it in terms of
通常您会从以下方面考虑
kind of different different the way I
我的方式有些不同
think about different views of the
考虑不同的看法
application so if you're building an
应用程序，因此，如果您要构建一个
e-commerce application you have
您拥有的电子商务应用程序
customers that's one thing to look at
客户是一回事
you have orders you have products even
您有订单甚至有产品
with a product you might have reviews
使用您可能有评论的产品
for the product details for the product
有关产品的产品详细信息
inventory levels for the product and
产品的库存水平和
those are three different ways of
那是三种不同的方式
looking at a product that would be
看一个会
multiple services because your inventory
多种服务，因为您的库存
system is completely independent of
系统完全独立于
reviews that happen to be written about
碰巧写的评论
that product so they don't need to be in
该产品，因此他们不需要进入
the same service they don't belong in
他们不属于的相同服务
the same service so you would break
同样的服务，所以你会打破
those apart okay I think that's I think
那些分开，好吧，我认为那是我认为
that's about it we'll be here for a bit
就是这样，我们会在这里待一会儿
otherwise thank you very much have a
否则非常感谢你有一个
great rest of the conference if we don't
如果我们不参加会议的其余时间
see you again
再见
you
您